Summer... will be
over soon.
What was I doing
this summer?
My mama died, so I went
to live with "him".
We fought a lot.
I kissed Rintarô-senpai.
Thanks.
Your dad is cool.
He's young at heart.
I envy you, Marimo.
I liked his dark side...
and his beard.
Rintarô-senpai seems to want to
see me to talk about him.
Is that right? So you're
not calling him "papa" yet.
You should. That would
make Shinpei happy.
I don't like it. Everyone
brings "him" up.
- Watch the house today.
- Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to the onsen.
I'm going to use that
overnight trip for two
- to the onsen with Asami.
- You said you'd take me.
- I'm taking Asami.
- You said you'd take me!
See you!
Liar.
I don't care about you.
What is it?
Shinpei... died.
His motorcycle
was totaled.
There was no way he
could've survived that.
He said he was going
to take you, after all.
So he turned back.
I see. So you are
crying. Are you sad?
Why didn't you
call him "papa"?
He was working his
hardest after he took you in.
Yet you...
Shinpei won't find peace.
But...
Did I cry?
Did I cry for him?
No way.
- Good morning!
- You're full of spirit!
I dreamed that I got the part
for the Muscle Museum!
- Oh, really?
- You and I passed.
Did I pass it, too?
It'll come true then!
A dream-come-true?
A dream-come-true,
huh. No way.
HITONATSU NO PAPA E
MATSUSHIGE YUTAKA
KITAGAWA HIROMI
TSUGUMI
MATSUDA SATOSHI
ICHIHARA HAYATO
KOBAYASHI CHIHARU
YAMANAKA SÔ
KINBARA YASUNARI
TSUNOMURA MAKO
TOYOKAWA EIJUN
HIRANUMA NORIHISA
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
Directed by
KARAKI AKIHIRO
FINAL:
SUTEKI NA OMOIDE O
ARIGATÔ... PAPA
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Marimo-chan, what's that?
Hello.
I see. So you're worried
about Shinpei.
So you're being a good
daughter to him.
Have you called
him "that"?
- What's "that"?
- Papa.
Have you called
him "papa"?
Are you still referring
to him as just "him"?
You should call him "papa."
It'll make him happy.
I saw this scene
in my dream.
TALSIMAN FOR ROAD SAFETY
Marimo-chan!
Isn't today the day they're
announcing the audition results?
I wonder if I passed. I've
been excited since this morning.
Why would you pass?
Didn't I dance great
on center stage?
- You were just in the way.
- I thought I danced pretty well.
Yes, I understand.
Thank you.
Who was that call from?
Is it for the Muscle
Museum musical?
Kôji, congratulations.
Did I pass?
- I did it!
- What about me?
Ponta, Chôko, and
Kikugorô also passed.
We did it!
What about me?
What are you
talking about?
Try harder next time.
- Four out of seven passed!
- That's awesome!
You'll all become stars.
Don't forget us now.
I'll go see it with my
co-workers at the station.
Wait, Jun!
Don't sulk like that!
This isn't your last chance!
I know that!
Then congratulate the
ones that have passed.
Isn't that friendship?
I'm hungry so I'm going
out to eat a beef bowl.
They're hopeless.
Think so?
They're just frustrated.
The three of us failed.
But that's the result.
If you sulk, then they
can't be openly happy.
I know that.
Then you should...
Shinpei, you're cold.
That was an awful
thing to say.
I thought you understood
the pains of others.
Marimo-chan, what's wrong?
I see. That's harsh.
How can he say that
to the people who failed?
That was mean. I feel
disappointed in him.
Is Shinpei at fault?
Do you think he would
say such a mean thing?
I think he was just trying
to encourage them.
And to tell them to be happy
for their friends' success.
He wants them
to strive harder.
He should just say that.
He's a man of few words.
Where did he go? I want
to apologize to him.
I was busy looking
all over for that cat today.
- I feel hungry.
- Sorry about earlier.
I don't think you're
wrong in what you said.
So don't let it get to you.
Are you trying
to cheer me up?
So you have
a sweet side to you.
Stop kissing me,
you pervert.
You're hurting me!
- Make me something.
- We only have leftovers.
Will you make me
something? I'm famished.
Excuse me. It's time
for us to close.
- They can stay.
- OK.
They'll be working
here from next week.
- Can we look around?
- Sure.
I wanted them to check out
the pub's atmosphere today.
So they're scouting.
the place.
What do you mean by
they're going to work here?
They're replacing Kikugorô,
Ponta, Kôji and Chôko.
Are they going to quit?
I said nothing
about quitting.
- That's a mean joke!
- That's not funny at all!
Are you taking the
stage practice lightly?
How many days do you
think you'll be practicing?
Two months!
You'll be practicing hard
for two months straight,
day in and day out!
You didn't have time to be
dancing here, in between.
Wait a minute, Manager!
I'm going to lose
four people.
I have to find
replacements.
- I'll work both sides.
- Get realistic!
I'm running
a business here.
I can't let a tired
person up on stage.
It's rude to
the customers!
It's time to say goodbye.
I don't want to leave here.
Here's the key. Be sure
to lock up after you.
Manager!
Kikugorô, you've
stepped up the ladder.
But... I never thought
about leaving here.
What is your dream?
To work here?
That's no it, is it?
Isn't it your dream to
dance on a huge stage?
If you think of this place as
someplace you can fall back on,
then it's over for you.
I'm the only person who
can always stay here.
The rest of you have
to leave here someday.
That's true.
I'll try hard to graduate from
here as soon as possible.
I think I'll be first.
Kikugorô, we'll
come after you.
We'll get a part in a
different stage production.
So as graduates of this
pub, live proud to our name.
We don't want this place
to have a bad reputation.
When you get famous...
Be sure to advertise
this place.
Then we'll get a lot
of customers.
- Manager...
- Stop crying.
The manager is nice.
When your pursue
your dreams...
You have to go
through farewells, too.
What do I want to do?
Don't feel rushed.
Life is long.
Take it slowly.
Do you understand?
That hurts. Stop it.
Good morning.
Are you going
to school from today?
Bye!
A school uniform...
It's been a long
time since I wore one.
If she's going to school...
- Delicious!
- I'm glad.
Why are you here though?
I thought you might need
breakfast, since Marimo-chan
is going to school now.
Does school start today?
Is it just you and me?
It's not even noon yet.
Please have
something to drink.
Are you Marimo's
school teacher?
How embarrassing.
What is your
relationship to Marimo-san?
I'm her father.
You have a different
surname from her.
There's a reason for that.
It's a problem to have
a young girl living in
an immoral
environment as this.
- Are you after her fortune?
- What?
Are you after her mother's
insurance proceeds?
This hag has got the nerve.
I'm going to bring this up
as a problem at school.
I'll just register her
as my daughter then.
It it wrong for me
to have a girlfriend?
- Let me go!
- What's with you?
Are you trying to get
between Marimo and me?
Are you getting
violent with me?
You're hurting me!
You're a failure
as a parent!
A failure?
Don't let that get to you.
I'm going.
Hey! Don't go
to the school.
I'm going to the
ward office.
I'll register her
as my daughter.
I'm going.
Why? She's my daughter!
Not an adopted daughter!
I want to register her.
Please submit evidence
that she's your daughter.
Sensei!
He's in a meeting right
now. You can't go in.
They're discussing
something important.
I'll just ask you.
I want to register
Marimo as my daughter.
I don't know the
procedures to do it.
Sensei! Please!
Please help me!
My advice to you as
a retained attorney is...
You have no choice but
to close down that pub.
The owner is to
blame for it all.
You won't be able to give
them any severance pay,
but you can at least
pay them their wages.
But next month, when
the debtors put a lien on
everything, you won't be
able to pay them a cent.
If me work hard
this month...
It's impossible.
The owner got
hooked on gambling.
So he borrowed money
using that pub as collateral.
I'm at a loss now.
Things were just
starting to look bright.
With Kikugorô and the
others going out in the world...
We were starting to get
a steady crowd of customers.
We were covered by the media
as the place they trained at.
And...
I'm bummed.
Everyone worked
so hard at it.
Ten million yen.
The loan is for
ten million yen?
There's nothing
you can do about it.
It's not something you
should get involved in.
But...
If that pub closes down...
Koba-san will lose his dream.
It's not your duty
to look after his life.
He danced in front
of his daughter recently.
When I saw him dancing
passionately for his daughter...
I wanted him to rise
victorious in life.
Rise victorious in life?
After working for you as
an investigator, I realized
that you have to win in
court or it means nothing.
If you don't win, then
you will end up a loser.
So to win, I did anything
and everything.
Even sleazy things.
Sotokoba should
live his own life.
You have to live
for Marimo-chan.
I can't ignore my
friend in distress.
Where is it?
Are you after her fortune?
So he was fooling around
with a woman in this room.
Do I have to keep a
constant eye on him?
What are you doing here?
He's not home.
Didn't second
semester start?
What are you going to do?
Go to college or go to work?
Did you come
here for me?
Of course. I'm worried.
I haven't decided yet.
Why?
Before summer, I was
determined to go to college.
But now, I'm wondering if
there's any meaning to going
to college when I don't
know what I want out of life.
That's what I learned
from working there.
Everyone has a dream... and
is striving hard towards it.
That made me want to be
engrossed in something, too.
What do you want to do?
I don't know yet.
That sounds deep.
I met a lot of strange
people this summer.
That sounds nice.
You're great.
I feel like hugging
you tightly.
Shinpei-chan!
What were you doing?
What were you trying to do?
- Did you drag in a guy?
- It's not what you think!
What are you doing
behind her father's back!?
- Why are you here?
- I'm going to get fired.
My superior thinks I'm
working on the side.
Remember the time
I danced at the pub?
A civilian who saw that
reported it to my superior.
I said I wasn't working there,
but they wouldn't believe me.
I have absolutely no
interest in dancing!
What do you mean?
You were really into it.
A big job?
- Are you out of money?
- That's right.
You're the only one
that I can turn to.
Refer me to someone who
will pay me ten million yen.
Ten million yen?
You have the right
contacts, don't you?
- Will this guy do?
- Yes, he'll do.
Can we trust this
bearded guy to do it?
There's no one else!
If we succeed, we can
live it up in Thailand!
They want you to steal
Hokuto Kôsan's microchip.
- Am I going to be a thief?
- An industry spy.
They'll pay you five
million yen upfront,
and the rest when
the job is done.
If you tell anyone,
we'll kill you.
Will you hear me out?
I don't know what to do.
Sorry, but I'm going
to be busy from now.
Where's the flashlight?
Do you know where
the flashlight is?
Did you touch this?
What were you
going to do with Mama's
insurance proceeds?
Well...
What's the big deal?
I only touched it.
You can use it.
If you really need the
money, you can use it.
But I want to know what
you're going to use it for.
I want to know. Aren't
we father and daughter?
Well, it's for...
Asami-chan,
what are you doing?
If that pub closes down...
Koba-san will lose his dream.
Marimo-chan, we're
about to open shortly.
Why do I have
to tell you?
I want to know.
- I just need the money!
- That doesn't tell me anything!
It's for our living expenses.
That's being cowardly
as a parent.
Stay out of this.
I don't need to give a reason
to use my child's money.
Will you hand over those
insurance proceeds?
You said I could use it.
Will you lend it to me?
Why won't you tell
me the truth?
Stop acting big in front
of me as a father.
You don't show me
your true feelings.
I can't be a real
family with you.
Marimo-chan,
you've got it wrong.
He went to the ward
office today to register you
as his own daughter.
Don't say
unnecessary things.
Register me?
Don't act on
your own like that.
What's with you?
Don't decide such
important things on your own!
I am not one of your belongings!
I hate you.
Go ahead and use it,
if you want.
How lucky for me!
Shinpei, you're the worst.
If you use that money, you
will become a rotten person.
Shinpei?
I know that.
Shinpei! What
happened? Tell me!
He's like a child.
Konari-san.
Where's Shinpei?
He went out.
Will you give this to him?
What is it for?
It's the money
for your dream.
Shinpei, I turned that deal
down and returned the money.
It sounds too dangerous,
no matter how I look at it.
Where's Shinpei?
Oh, no! What am
I going to do?
- Did Shinpei go? Stop him!
- What's going on?
Tell me what's going on.
Where did Shinpei go?
See you!
I hate you.
Well, it's for...
If you don't talk to me,
how am I supposed to know!
Marimo-chan...
Shinpei is...
- What is his condition?
- We're still treating him.
What's going on?
I just came from the site!
His motorcycle was totaled.
There's no way he
can survive that!
It's my fault.
No, it's not. It's my fault.
Will you be quiet?
We're in a hospital.
His pulse isn't coming back.
I'm a doctor. Please let
me go inside and watch.
Please put this
somewhere on his body.
Please save him.
I'll hold on to it.
My daughter?
Are you serious?
That's a harsh joke!
- Are you going to take it?
- You told me to take it.
- That's my entire fortune!
Don't do to others what you
don't want done to you. Stupid.
Will you lock the door!
Marimo, you were
conceived with all of our love.
Please believe me.
I really didn't do it.
I can swear to you!
Why did you
hurt my Marimo!?
It'll heal right away.
One gets irate
when one is hungry.
Don't hold back and eat.
Take me to
someplace fancier.
How old do you
think you are?
What's so good about
an ordinary life?
It's rough being a parent.
Be my parent.
Don't leave me alone.
Don't leave me alone!
Don't die!
I don't want to be alone!
After Mama died...
All my relatives rejected me.
But you took me in.
That made me happy...
very happy!
I felt I wasn't alone anymore.
That feeling made me
very happy.
I've been enjoying it lately.
I've been enjoying
spending time with you.
So I don't want to be
alone anymore!
Live... for me!
I have a lot to apologize
to you about.
I haven't called you "papa" yet.
So please...
Shinpei, come back.
Shinpei!
WE'RE HAVING A FAREWELL
AND SEND-OFF PARTY TODAY
Thank you for coming
when you're busy.
- Satoi-san.
- Why did Shinpei...
Satoi, what're you
doing here?
When I think about Marimo-chan,
who is left all alone...
I don't know what to say.
Hey, Shinpei is here.
Yes, he's here. He was
discharged today.
Discharged? What is
this send-off party for?
Aren't they overdoing it?
They should be celebrating
my hospital discharge.
- Hey!
- It's the loser!
What's going on?
I thought you died.
Why are you alive?
Why am I here?
I'm immortal.
Stop joking around.
Satoi, I got to see you again!
That makes me so happy!
Congratulations on your
hospital discharge.
How considerate of you!
A onsen trip for two!
Isn't this the one
I bought before?
Go with Asami-san.
- What a kid.
- I feel bad.
So you've grown up.
Don't you have something
else to say to him?
Remember what
you said that day?
- Forget that.
- What is it?
- Go ahead and say it.
- Come out with it.
- Now is your chance.
- What is it? Tell me.
Are you all having
nice dreams?
This is a send-off party
for the four who will be
turning their dreams
into reality.
But this won't be farewell.
This is just their departure!
And this will be their last
stage performance here!
Dreams are there
to be realized.
Let's dance till we drop!
Congratulations on your
hospital discharge, Papa.
So you said it.
I didn't hear it too well.
Can you say it again?
No.
I found a dream.
I'm going to be a nurse,
just like my mama.
Come and work for me then.
HAKUAI NURSING SCHOOL
I found a dream for myself.
I am leaving this place today.
Are you going to be
lonely without me?
It'll be a big relief.
Likewise.
Can a spoiled brat like
you survive in a dorm?
Oh, be quiet.
You can still
change your mind.
I'll make my
dream come true.
Thanks for all
you've done.
See you.
My summer is about
to come an end.
With all that's happened,
I had the best summer ever.
That's because
I met you, Papa.
2014-11