I'm late!
EVICTION NOTICE:
PLEASE LEAVE BY JULY 31ST.
I don't believe this.
This isn't good.
I'm late from the first day.
I don't believe this.
The guy I liked a year
ago was there.
Marimo.
Are you taking summer
lectures, too?
I want to go to the same
college as Rintarô.
See you later.
Bye.
Is that right?
I have to go to the
registration office.
We haven't received it yet.
I don't believe this...
There's been no payment?
We received you application
for it, but we haven't
received payment for it.
So you can't attend
the lecture today.
Please submit
payment immediately.
Yes.
Julianne, it's time to eat.
So the payment wasn't made...
I woke up late...
and rushed all the way here.
But I couldn't attend class.
Rintarô-senpai is
dating Satsuki.
And there was that
eviction notice on my door.
This is a bad day for me.
Aren't you going
to attend your lecture?
I'm in trouble.
What's wrong?
I've fallen for you.
I don't believe this!
This is the start of a
confusing summer break.
HITONATSU NO PAPA E
MATSUSHIGE YUTAKA
KITAGAWA HIROMI
TSUGUMI
MATSUDA SATOSHI
ÔSAWA MIKIO
ICHIHARA HAYATO
HIROOKA YURIKO
SUGATA SHUN
KOBAYASHI CHIHARU
YAMANAKA SÔ
KINBARA YASUNARI
TSUNOMURA MAKO
TOYOKAWA EIJUN
HIRANUMA NORIHISA
SAWAJIRI ERIKA
USUDA ASAMI
KOIDE YUKA
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
Directed by
HIROKI RYÛICHI
EPISODE 2:
MOMEN NO HANKACHÎFU
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
This isn't good, after all...
Let's take a break
until show time!
Sotokoba-san, this
is about my friend...
She was kissed by her
friend's boyfriend.
What do you think
of that?
What do you mean?
Should she tell her
friend about it?
That's a difficult one.
Why should she?
What? Wouldn't you
normally do that?
Does she tell her friend?
- That's not a good idea.
- It's not?
It'll only hurt her friend.
What if she accuses her
of seducing him?
I think the problem lies
in how that girl, who was
kissed, feels about him.
That's true.
You're smart. I guess
wisdom comes with age.
Does your friend
like that guy?
A little.
That's complicated!
It's a love triangle!
So does she tell her
friend or not?
Shinpei is good at
those things.
Shinpei's good at it.
Never mind him.
Should we have left
him to Shinpei?
Will you calm down a bit?
How can I?
Our fate lies on it.
We left our key witness to an
important case to Shinpei.
How can I remain calm?
Don't yell at me.
Do you want to know
what the case is about?
- No.
- I'll tell you.
"A" who borrowed money
from the loanshark,
committed suicide a year ago.
"B" who is that man's son,
blames the collectors' harsh
methods for his father's death.
He stabbed the man in
charge of the collections.
Then the loanshark reported
him for attempted murder.
We'll be defending
"B" in this case.
The date of the trail
is coming up.
And we're having this man,
Ebihara Masaru, who worked
for that loanshark company
part-time, stand as witness.
Did he turn them in?
We want to expose their
harsh collection methods
with Ebihara's testimony.
We'll ask the court
to take the extenuating
circumstances
into consideration.
We'll show the media our abilities
and increase our clientele.
- That's the game plan.
- Wow.
There's a problem though.
There's a bunch that can't
afford to have him testify.
And rumor has it that
they are after his life.
Killers?
Shinpei has him in his custody
until the day of the trail.
He's the bodyguard?
Shinpei is groovy.
What's so groovy about him?
I'm completely worried!
Do you think that
unshaved good-for-nothing
can handle a major
job like this?
- Satoi.
- Yes?
It all starts with trust.
But Shinpei is...
I'm here with the bentô.
Leave them there.
So you're being a filial
daughter to him.
She's just doing her job.
Dr. Asami, you must be
in a fix to find out that
Shinpei has a child.
- Why is that?
- Are you acting tough?
Oh, is that how you're
going to come out?
This is the first time
we're formally meeting.
Hello.
Let's eat!
Eh, bad news!
Go back and work!
What a way to talk to her.
There's no loving feeling.
You have to be kind to her.
She shouldn't be seeing
something like this.
Is that so?
Is that your comeback?
- I want to talk to you.
- No.
Let's play again.
I want child support.
What?
I won't collect for the
past, so can you start
paying me from this month?
You've got it wrong there.
Stop kidding around.
I'm serious.
Child support?
If you can afford to bet
10,000 or 20,000 yen on
mahjong, can you
give it to me instead?
You show up all of a sudden
and claim to be my daughter.
Then you tell me your mama
died and you want child support.
Did you honestly think
I'd readily agree to it?
Do I look like
Daddy Long Legs?
You're my father.
- Who do you think you are?
- Your daughter.
So you're going
to come on strong?
This is my entire fortune.
Take it.
- Are you going to take it?
- You said to take it.
- That's all that I have!
- But you said to take it!
- Are you a demon?
- Don't accuse me of that.
- What are you thinking of?
- I want it!
- Stop being money crazy!
- I want to attend prep school.
And I want to move houses!
But I don't have any money.
All right!
Wait until I complete
this job.
Good luck with work...
...and at being a papa.
See you later.
Sorry to tease you earlier.
It's all right.
Take it. You deserve
to have it.
He ignored you until now.
Put it away before your
dad gets back.
Trouble!
Trouble?
They're going to kill me.
You're going to get killed?
I'm definitely going
to get killed!
- What's up?
- They're here!
- They're going to kill me!
- Let's go up!
- Where are we going?
- Hide there.
Hurry!
We're safe here.
They don't know
about this place.
What a scare!
Don't worry.
- Say...
- What?
Is there a reason why
I had to run away?
It doesn't concern me,
does it?
Yes, it doesn't.
I can't stand this.
Why are you at my home?
We have nowhere else to go.
This is the only place
I could think of.
What's wrong?
You have a point.
Let's go.
Where? I don't want
to move from here.
- Just come!
- What if I get killed?
I'll protect you,
even if I die.
If you get killed,
you can't protect me.
Stop getting smart!
You can stay here today.
Shinpei disappeared?
When I went to check up
on him at his room,
his place was ransacked.
Is Ebihara missing, too?
Yes. They were most
likely taken away.
Can't he even do a
babysitting job properly!?
Who are you men?
Are you Konari-san?
I'm asking you who you are!
Shut up, small fry!
Have a seat.
Let's strike a deal.
Will you hand over Ebihara?
My boss is willing
to pay 100 million yen.
It's not a bad deal, is it?
Let me think about it.
We'll be waiting
for a good response.
What's going on?
Shinpei hasn't been caught.
He's doing his job.
A 100 million yen, huh.
This is getting to be
interesting.
Shinpei isn't here.
Is that right?
Dr. Asami, aren't you...
What is it?
Isn't he here?
I wanted to talk to him.
I thought he'd know how
it is as a new father.
My daughter gets
violent in the home.
She's at a defiant age.
She doesn't even tell us
when she leaves the house.
So I have to chase after
her and scold her for it.
Manager!
Why won't you talk to me?
This is scary.
EVICTION NOTICE
Hey!
Isn't it dangerous to be
out here during the day?
It's easier to get lost
in the crowd.
I get your point.
You needn't tag along.
I don't want to be
home all alone.
Go somewhere else.
Like prep school.
I need money for it.
I can't attend classes
until I pay the tuition.
I'm hungry.
Let's grab something to eat.
Sure.
- Money.
- I have none.
What happened
to the money?
I don't have it.
I left it at your place.
Don't just leave it.
Why didn't you bring it?
You're so stupid.
How are we going to eat?
Let's go mug someone.
That's young.
That's all I can think of.
That's true.
OK.
Don't agree to it.
We're in the midst of
a battle now.
We can't go to battle
on an empty stomach.
How old are you?
I'm 38.
I found a perfect victim!
Stop it!
Give me 10,000 yen!
Or 5,000 yen!
Even 3,000 yen will do!
Don't pick on me.
Koba-san?
What's going on here?
Audition?
It's for a musical.
Is that right?
That's awesome!
It's my dream.
- That's great!
- Fantastic!
I have to get the part first.
We're starting the audition
for numbers 30 through 40!
I'm going.
When I see people talking
about their dreams,
it makes me upset.
I used to be a dancer.
You?
What're you laughing about?
But once you hurt
yourself, that's it.
It's unsightly.
Your Achilles' tendon?
I started dancing from
when I was in middle school.
It was my dream to dance in major
stage productions and in New York City.
But it ended with a snap.
I can never forget
that snapping sound.
It was telling me
to give up on my dream.
After that, I went reckless.
That's how I ended up
at that place.
The loanshark company?
I picked on the weak...
and acted like the big guy.
I started wondering
what I was doing.
What is my life all about?
Don't get jealous of others.
I know.
I know!
What is it?
I have a good idea.
The rhythm for the audition.
I was nervous.
I'm sure you did fine.
- Think so?
- You danced well.
Thanks for saying that.
It's hard to realize
your dreams.
That's probably why you
can strive very hard.
Do you have a dream?
My dream...
Marimo!
They're my friends.
I'm going over to talk to them.
Sorry.
As for prep school...
Is that your papa?
He doesn't look
sharp at all.
Is he really a private eye?
No, he's...
Rintarô!
Did you wait long?
No.
- See you later.
- Bye!
Did you hear about Satsuki?
She's trying hard to get
into the same college as him.
Did you know?
Marimo went out to make
a delivery yesterday and
she never came back.
Is that right?
She probably thinks the
hourly pay here it too low.
Will you consider raising
my hourly rate first?
Manager!
What happened to you?
I'm sorry. I got caught
up with things.
You're getting a hourly
wage reduction.
I'll raise it by 50 yen!
Why are you with
Sotokoba-san?
Are you two seeing
each other?
Are you really?
She went to the audition
with me to give me support.
Sotokoba-san was great.
Audition? What do you mean?
It's for this!
- A musical!
- So you went to take it?
That's awesome.
- Where is he?
- Who?
Where were you? I was
looking all over for you.
I was busy.
Will you watch him dance?
Who is he?
My friend.
His name is Ebihara.
Nice to meet you!
He's good.
That's it!
You're pretty good.
It was easy to dance
with him.
It was fun.
Did you get your
child support?
Not yet.
He's hopeless.
Aren't the people
here nice?
They give me energy.
Are you seeing him?
What does it seem like?
I'm asking you.
It's hard to say.
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
It's about my friend.
She was kissed by her
friend's boyfriend.
It's a love triangle...
and it's complex.
Should she tell her
friend about it?
Hello?
Shinpei! Where are you?
Is Ebihara safe?
The trail is tomorrow!
That's a lot of questions.
Answer me!
Is Ebihara safe?
He's as safe as he can be.
Will you chill down?
Ebihara said to tell you
to deposit the money.
What is he talking about?
We promised to pay him
an appreciation fee
on the day before the trail.
Make sure you deposit
that by today.
I'll be sure to take him
to the courtroom at
10:00 sharp tomorrow.
Don't screw up now!
What's wrong?
This...
Tomorrow?
Shinpei!
Will you look at this?
It's to the Philippines.
It's for the 10:00 am
fight tomorrow.
Isn't he going to dance
here with us?
Stop touching my stuff.
What's the meaning of this?
Tomorrow is the day
of the trail.
You weren't planning
to show up?
How can I make
a testimony like that?
They're very dangerous.
Did you deceive me?
Ebihara!
Did you swindle money
from Konari-san,
just to raise money
to flee the country?
What are you afraid
of at this point?
Shut up.
Shut up!
Ebihara!
Why do you deceive people?
Get a grip! He ran away?
We already deposited the
money into his account.
Are you in cahoots with him?
Are you kidding?
I'm very sorry!
I promise to bring him back!
Please tell me the address
of the company he worked for.
Stupid. They're yakuza.
Do you honestly think you
can get him back alone?
Will you shut up!
Konari-san!
If you go, you'll get killed.
I'll go.
It's my job.
What are you thinking of?
Don't be reckless.
- Get off my case, stupid.
- You're going to get killed!
Stop following me.
He deceived you! Why should
you have to go to save him?
Marimo!
I promised him I'd
protect him even if I die.
I'll protect you,
even if I die.
I have to keep my promises.
But...
Besides, I will get
paid for it.
Are you stupid?
I'll be sure to send
you to prep school.
Just wait for me.
What are you doing?
Don't you have a gun?
Do you mean this?
Yes, this!
Not a real one! A fake!
Hey! When are you
going there again?
You've got guts, Ebihara.
We knew that you weren't
planning to testify.
If we get prosecuted,
so will you.
You're not one who can
live such a courageous life.
Give us back the floppy disk
with the clients' addresses.
Give us back the money
source data that you stole!
I don't want to corner people
to their deaths anymore.
I don't want to see
that happen again!
Get real!
When did you turn into
a righteous guy!?
Are we wrong?
It's the people who don't pay
back their loans that are at fault!
Am I wrong about that?
Hey!
- Who are you?
- Ebihara's partner.
Are you OK?
Are you the fools that's
been sheltering him?
Don't move!
Koba-san.
Put that on!
Put your hands up!
Koba-san.
Hurry!
Light each other's
candles!
Hurry!
Put your hands up!
Put them down!
Up, again! To the side!
Don't move!
Stay still!
Ebihara, come this side.
Koba-san.
Are you OK?
You're late.
Shinpei!
Ouch!
Bam! Bam! Bam!
How dare you take
us for fools!
I'm going to get you!
Will you chill down?
Let's talk this over.
I'm sorry.
Is that your occupation?
You're great!
SHIBAURA CLINIC
Ouch!
Aren't you going
to use anesthesia?
- No.
- Why not?
It's a waste.
I don't believe this.
Will you pay me?
Sorry.
What are you doing?
Is this where he hid it?
It's an inconvenience.
He must've had faith.
Thank you.
Say...
What?
Is he your friend?
Yes.
When he deceived you?
I want to associate with
him for life, so he is.
See you.
A friend...
The floppy diskette.
Shinpei did a good job.
COURTHOUSE
What took you so long?
- Oh, he's hurt.
- Hurry!
You call yourself a
bodyguard, making him hurt?
And you're late.
Come 30 minutes
early next time.
Let's grab a drink later.
Are you listening?
We don't have time. Hurry.
Even if I get arrested,
you'll be my friend,
won't you?
I sure wish I could've
danced more!
See you later.
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
It's about my friend.
Will you listen to me?
Shut up.
Don't tell me to shut up.
Will you listen to me?
What is it? Are you stupid?
Don't confide in people
about things like that.
It's important! She was
kissed by him!
Decide for yourself if you
want love or friendship.
How can you say that...
Do you know it's about me?
It's obvious.
Are you stupid?
This is the money for
your prep school.
Julianne doesn't look
peppy. Hang in there.
Are you going to pay
for it or not?
Can I think about it
for a minute?
Can you skip class?
I want to associate with him
for life, so he's a friend.
Satsuki is a friend I want
to associate with for life.
I don't care who you fall
in love with,
but don't  break up my
friendship with Satsuki.
Julianne, hang in there.
EVICTION NOTICE
I didn't have money
to pay for that, too.
You can come
to live with me.
Those words were warmer
than the warm weather today.
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
A Production of
JOKER & TBS
2014-08