Mama, it's goodbye
to this room.
The room filled with
memories of you.
I'm going to live
with him from today.
This is my new home.
I'll be living with
the man that you loved.
What are you doing?
Don't put it there.
Put it in your own room.
What do you mean?
Didn't I tell you before?
Don't come into my life.
It's a photo of my mama.
I know.
It's the photo of the
woman you loved.
She's someone of my past.
How can you say that?
Don't put it here.
I don't want any "family"
feeling in this room.
Your room is there.
Go.
What's with that look?
You'll chase the men away.
Shut up! What does it
matter to you?
Ugly!
Don't call me ugly!
What happened with your
friend's boyfriend?
Was that about you?
She was kissed by her
friend's boyfriend!
This is the pits.
It was a mistake to move here.
HITONATSU NO PAPA E
MATSUSHIGE YUTAKA
KITAGAWA HIROMI
TSUGUMI
MATSUDA SATOSHI
ICHIHARA HAYATO
KOBAYASHI CHIHARU
MITSUISHI KEN
MIYATA SANAE
YAMANAKA SÔ
KINBARA YASUNARI
TSUNOMURA MAKO
TOYOKAWA EIJUN
HIRANUMA NORIHISA
NATSUYAGI ISAO
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
Directed by
YOSHIMURA TATSUYA
EPISODE 3:
CHIISA NA KOI NO UTA
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Who's this?
Sendô Kenkichi...
A man the Sensei
defended ten years ago.
He has a hairy chest.
He's nicknamed as
Wild Horse Senkichi.
He beat seven gangsters
to a pulp in a fight.
He's coming out
of jail tomorrow.
Don't let someone
like him out of jail.
Your job it to watch
over him.
He said he was going to
get even when he got out.
But we don't know who
he's planning to go after.
That's what we want
to find out.
- That's for the police to do.
- It's the Sensei's order!
Just do as you're told!
Don't help yourself
to coffee!
Wild Horse Senkichi, huh...
He's old already.
What are you doing,
old man?
Give us your money,
if you don't want to die.
Amateurs like you shouldn't
be flinging this around, or
you might get into trouble.
I'm sorry.
He's cool!
"Amateurs like you shouldn't
be flinging this around, or
you might get into trouble."
That's really cool.
Who are you?
Who told you to tail me?
You're going to get it!
I'll tell you!
Who is he?
There's a reason for this.
What're you doing there?
Come here quickly.
It's a request from Senkichi-san.
Prepare it right.
I can't cook.
So Konari-san asked you
to watch me.
He was afraid that you might
go out and get even.
Don't be ridiculous.
Do you want me to go back
to jail at this age?
I've had enough of jail life.
That's true.
He's such a worrywart.
I like the way you gulp
down your liquor.
You're a real man.
Bring another bottle
of beer.
What're you doing?
Bring us a bottle of beer.
Get it yourself.
I'm not your maid!
What a way to speak
to your father!
- What?
- What!?
Will you give it to her?
How pathetic.
Truly pathetic!
I'm disappointed in you.
She's not properly
disciplined!
And you!
What a way to speak
to your father!
To set the record straight,
I only found out three weeks
ago that he's my father!
And I'm not legally
registered as his daughter.
A lot has been happening.
I see... is that what happened?
You're a man to take
that big step.
It's hard to live under
such circumstances.
You must've really been
in love with that woman.
Who is she?
Well, she's my...
How can you see another
woman, when you have the
daughter of your loved one!
Don't say that in front
of Asami.
Excuse me.
Asami-chan, are you leaving?
Are you in shock?
Didn't I tell you so?
I was wondering how
you'd react if I called you
"Asami-chan," instead
of the formal "Dr. Asami."
Sorry about that. Sotokoba-chan
is in a good mood today.
I got a part in the musical.
Wow!
I've started my
lessons from today.
Great!
We have another
interesting piece of news.
What is it?
We saw a photo
of Shinpei's old lover.
Marimo-chan's mother.
There was a photo in
Shinpei's room.
Not that I care.
Bye.
That was a bad response.
She might be in greater
shock than she let out.
Living alone...
I made a mistake.
- Please be my guarantor.
- What?
Listen. A father has
to set his foot down!
That's all it takes.
I get it.
That would work best in
education a child.
What if she gets defiant?
- Give it to her.
- With this?
The minute she defies you,
she becomes the enemy.
Should a man show
his back to the enemy?
The answer is no.
I've learned a lot from you.
By the way, who are you?
I have some happy news!
You rat! Is this where
you were hiding?
A guarantor for
an apartment?
Are you going
to move out of here?
I don't think it's going
to work out, after all.
We've led separate lives
for the past 17 years.
I see.
You scared me!
Does he look like
the guy that you hate?
He looks exactly like him!
His name is Traitor Masa.
He goes on in life
betraying people.
When I saw his face before
me, it made me furious.
Sorry about that.
People tell me that
I have a peaceful face.
- What does he do?
- This.
Should I even be
associating with him?
Don't worry. What are
you saying?
Drink up... with your
own money.
Where are you taking me?
Don't look so worried.
Relax.
Sorry I'm late.
The night is young.
This is Senkichi-san.
- This is Ran.
- Hello.
He just came out of jail.
Give him a good workout.
This is something
small from me.
Shinpei, I'll just accept
the thought.
I'm sorry to have
wasted your time.
He's cool!
I really like his character.
They're all expensive.
I need to pay five months'
worth of rent up front.
He mistook me for
someone else and
he attacked me and
started choking me.
That scared the
wits out of me!
I see. So Yôko is
working as an OL now.
How is Tatsuo doing?
Has he made a career choice?
I haven't received this
month's child support yet.
Tatsuo is still in
high school.
Please keep your promise.
I didn't want you
to see that.
I'm sorry.
Aren't you
disappointed in me?
That's not...
That hesitation...
shows you think that.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
When I was let go
from my job, I thought...
If a company won't assure
me of lifetime employment...
Then for my next job, I want
to do something that I enjoy.
What do you enjoy?
Performing on stage.
That's been my dream
since I was little.
I understand now...
What?
...why there's an old
man at that club.
I'm sorry.
It's all right, even if
it bothers me a little.
I'm sorry.
Yes? It's me.
I didn't get the part
in the musical?
What do you mean by that?
I've already paid
my money!
Hello?
I don't buy that.
I just said, you failed.
I paid the money because
you said I passed.
I paid 300,000 yen for
my dancing, singing, and
acting lessons.
So?
So if I didn't pass,
refund me my money!
Please refund my money!
That was supposed
to go to my child support!
- It's not possible.
- What?
Did you read the contract?
Contract?
Damn!
Welcome back.
- Here.
- Thanks.
You're all dressed up today.
Can you tell?
I sure can. You look cute.
I bought it with my bonus!
Bonus? You got one?
When? When was this?
Sensei, I want to talk
to you.
Oh, you're in a meeting.
Excuse me.
Sorry for the interruption.
Why is Senkichi here?
Come in quietly!
Will you look at this?
What is it?
Senkichi-san!
I asked you to stay at home.
What are you doing here?
He came to pay his respects.
I owe it to Konari-san
that I made it out.
What are you panicking about?
Well, the situation is...
It does say so. Excuse me.
It's a typical case of fraud.
- What do you mean?
- We're having an audition.
There's going to be
an audition fee.
You've been qualified.
There's going to be
a fee for the lessons.
You lack the abilities
to keep up with the lessons.
You are now disqualified.
Thank you for your time.
But they told him he passed.
Look right here
in the fine print.
It's a pre-qualification.
That's not true!
They told me that I passed!
That is why it's a fraud.
What's not written here
will not hold in court.
That's the reality of it.
What's going to happen
to the money he paid?
Think of it as a lesson
fee in life.
How can you say that!
This isn't right!
Can't something be done?
We know that it's fraud.
On paper, it's not fraud!
You're useless.
If the law won't protect
you, then...
We'll just have to give
them an eye for an eye.
Let's go.
You can't stop me.
I'm going to get you
your money back.
If you go, you'll be
arrested by the police.
I don't care.
They took advantage
of my good friend's dream!
I'm not going
to forgive them for it!
Why don't you act
like a father?
Senkichi, don't give
him bad ideas.
I'm sorry.
That production company
is backed by Kuroisu Gang.
This is the worst
case scenario.
You won't get anything
back from them.
100,000 yen... is high!
I've fallen for you.
Marimo, I want
to talk to you.
I have nothing to say.
Wait.
- Wait!
- Let me go!
Why are you running away?
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do
to her when she's unwilling?
He's a pervert.
What?
So he did that to you when
he's dating your friend?
You did the right thing.
I did, didn't I?
You're not off track.
You're not a cat or a dog.
As a person, you must
exercise judgment.
But...
What are you
brooding about?
I'm wondering if my
mama was happy.
I wonder what kind
of love she had...
and why she decided
to have me alone...
I wonder how he feels
about my mama now.
There are too many
things I don't understand.
Cheer up.
Can I go to your room?
I don't feel like
dancing today.
Can I talk to you?
Marimo-chan is thinking
of living alone.
She asked me to be
her guarantor.
You?
- Is she here?
- Marimo?
She hasn't come yet.
Hey!
I see... A room...
Is that so?
I guess it won't be so
rosy from the start.
I see... So you've
been thinking about it...
It'll cost you a lot
of money to move.
Do you have money?
I have my mother's savings
and her life insurance proceeds.
Is that so? So you
have money.
Welcome back.
Is that Marimo-chan's mother?
Were you in love with her?
Never mind about that.
Let's go out to eat.
I was with Marimo-chan until now.
I heard a lot from her.
She's troubled.
If you took her in out
of sympathy...
then what you did
is a crime.
Hold her tightly in
your arms.
- Then it'll all be settled.
- Shut up.
It's none of your business.
I don't understand it.
I find out that I have
a daughter,
but her mother is dead.
What am I supposed to do?
I don't know what she
told you, but
don't tell me what to do.
There's no unity here!
We're not open yet!
How nice to have time
on your hands!
Can I get a drink?
What's wrong, Shinpei?
Are you running away?
Like you ran away
from the woman?
What an easy life you have!
Keep running away from the
rest of your life! You fool!
Don't give me that.
Who's running away?
Don't act as if you
know it all!
You're the one who's
leading an easy life!
running away in life!
You want to get even?
Then go!
If you think you're so
damn great, then
be my role model!
Don't switch the
story to me!
What's with you?
What's it to you?
Just leave me alone!
Your kid is crying!
She's suffering!
As a parent, help her!
Help her? What more
do you expect from me?
Shinpei, you really
don't know?
She was in front of
the realtor's office.
What are you unhappy
about with me?
When you said you wanted
to go to prep school,
I gave you the money
for it, didn't I?
When you had no place
to live, I offered you
my place, didn't I?
So what are you unhappy
about with me?
She doesn't need sympathy.
Just assume responsibility.
Assume the responsibility
of her life.
Give me a break, will you?
What wrong have I done?
Why am only I being blamed?
What's with you, anyway?
Why aren't you coming to me?
Why are you going to them?
You should tell me!
What am I to you? Damn it!
Why is it them?
You should just come to me!
How can she!
What do you mean by that?
What do you mean by that!?
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
Do you love my mama?
I want to know.
Why can't I leave
Mama's photo out?
I...
Why was I born?
Was I an "accident"?
Please tell me.
I...
...can't look at
Yukino's photo...
...when I think of how she
felt these past 17 years...
...and how she felt as she
raised you all these years.
It's very painful on me.
Yukino was a very
dear person to me.
You were...
...conceived with
all our love.
Mama...
Never mind already!
I'm sorry for being cocky!
Honesty is best, after all.
Yukino didn't come back.
She left Tokyo to care
for her ill mother...
...and she never came back.
I didn't see her after that.
I had no idea
she was pregnant.
Go back to her.
I have some work
to take care of first.
An eye for an eye.
I'll go alone.
I owe you one for the
lodging, so I'll go, too.
You're so cool.
He's a man, too.
You both came...
That makes me very happy.
Let's go.
That felt great!
Thank you very much.
Senkichi-san, you're
very strong.
I was shocked!
You were pretty
strong yourself.
I've fallen for you!
I have to go to work
now, so excuse me.
I'd better get going, too.
Where?
See you.
So you were here, after all.
So you're going now, after
you've paid your respects here?
I'm sorry. Please let me go.
Why do you dwell on the past?
You did as I told you.
There's someone who needs you.
Shinpei will be fine.
What're you talking about?
Konari-san asked me to look
after a stupid parent and child.
Is that the real reason?
I did it to repay my debt
to Konari-san.
Hang in there.
Don't gang up on me like that.
Masa who is with the
Kuroisu Gang used to be
my younger brother.
And he caused my
gang to disband.
I have to set things
straight as his big brother.
That fool.
He's always walked
a different path.
Shinpei, be a good father now.
Take his words to heart.
That's his final will.
Senkichi-san!
Is that true?
"Marimo, you were
conceived with all our love."
What an exaggerated act.
He really did say that.
Who's that?
Don't mind him.
He's a troubled crybaby.
I'll bring you another drink.
Good luck.
She's just a memory.
You're here in reality.
She might be
a formidable rival.
I'm on your side,
Asami-chenchei.
You're saying it funny.
Oh, really?
Kanpai.
Where's Shinpei-san?
- I don't know.
- That's cold.
I heard about it.
Don't ignore me!
Hi.
Where's Senkichi-san?
I thought he was with you.
He left on a trip.
Why?
Don't ever forget him.
Welcome, everyone!
We may have been bonded
by a single piece of paper.
But we don't need that
paper to be married.
Just as long as our hearts
are bonded together!
It's show time!
Tonight's theme is love!
Are you all having
your share of the love?
Let's have a grand
time tonight!
Mama, thank you.
I'm not alone.
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
YOSHIMURA TATSUYA
A Production of
JOKER & TBS
2014-09