The shape of fate...
might be that of
a triangle.
It must be a triangle.
We're not done
with you yet.
I'm not sure if it's
because of "him,"
but I seem to be heading
definitely towards doom.
Will you explain
things to us?
I... don't know myself.
- Didn't we break up?
- Is Marimo the reason?
That's not it, right?
Is it true that you
two kissed?
How do I explain that...
I...
I have nothing
to do with it.
Marimo!
I didn't do anything
wrong, did I?
So why am I running away?
Why am I making excuses?
This isn't good.
How are things going
as a police detective?
I need your help
on something.
Sorry. I'm busy with the
festival's security today.
I'll be right back.
Wait here.
I have something to discuss
with you, too. Wait here.
SMUGGLING DEAL AT 12:00 AM
Don't show up.
Why did you kill him?
Shut up. Let's get
out of here.
I've fallen in love
with you.
I guess I can't say it
doesn't concern me.
- Speed it up here!
- I don't like it.
I don't want to be caught.
How long are you going
to drive around here?
She saw us.
Who cares. Let's get
out of here for now.
How dangerous!
Fate is something
decided by God...
Or so, someone important
had said in a book.
Did I step on stool?
If this is my fate...
then God might be a bully.
HITONATSU NO PAPA E
MATSUSHIGE YUTAKA
KITAGAWA HIROMI
TSUGUMI
MATSUDA SATOSHI
ICHIHARA HAYATO
HAYASHI YASUFUMI
MASU TAKESHI
SHIMA DAISUKE
KOBAYASHI CHIHARU
YAMANAKA SÔ
KINBARA YASUNARI
TSUNOMURA MAKO
TOYOKAWA EIJUN
HIRANUMA NORIHISA
SAWAJIRI ERIKA
USUDA ASAMI
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
Directed by
MATSUNAGA YÔICHI
EPISODE 6:
OTONA NO KAKEHIKI
NANKA MITAKUNAI
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
TWO WOMEN FIGHT
OVER A MAN
This is terrible.
It's hot!
Will you be a bit
more considerate?
There's a lady here.
Don't be so conscious of
me because I'm sexy.
- I am your father.
- You know...!
What are you doing?
- I am the one paying for it.
- I'm the one who bought it.
Whatever that's in my
refrigerator belongs to me.
- You're not friendly at all.
- Don't you have any morals?
Even a cat will get attached
to you if you take care of it.
Well, excuse me. I'm a person.
- You're an irritating person.
- Not even close to you!
If you keep that up,
you'll never get a guy.
Well, excuse me, but that
isn't the case here.
Well, excuse me, excuse me!
Then get together with that
guy and live with him.
- You're such a vulgar father.
- Get off my case.
Hey, I'm a bachelor here!
Come here.
Clean out your ears
and listen up carefully.
After you came, there's been
no woman coming around!
That's because you
lack the appeal!
Don't blame it on me!
You're making me feel sick!
Put on your pants quickly!
Good morning!
Would you like to have
some shaved ice?
I heard it's a love triangle.
Did it hit you?
So what are you
going to do?
Well...
I know I have to set
things straight.
Are you in a love triangle?
You're not talking about me?
I thought you were talking
about Satsuki, Rintarô and me.
Isn't he your friend's
boyfriend that you kissed?
He's her ex-boyfriend.
- And he forced a kiss on me.
- Is that right?
- So it's a reckless relationship.
- Well, that's...
So you're doing
an immoral thing here.
I'm going to my part-time job.
Wretch!
So how are things with you?
I heard Asami-chan went
out with her former lover.
Word sure gets around fast.
Is that right? Am I fast
with the news?
This is the pits. I split
the beans from my side.
Now that "Is that right?"
lady knows about it.
This isn't looking good.
I'm going to forget about it.
I'm going to focus on my
part-time job today.
I don't believe it.
So they have days off.
What did you want to tell
me on our day off?
Don't you think they lack
the spirit these days?
- What do you mean?
- In their dancing.
There's no vigor or
radiance in their dance.
Maybe they're just tired.
It wasn't like that when
we first started this place.
There was passion and
ambition in everyone.
Everyone was radiant.
So I'm thinking of asking
one person to leave.
- Marimo-chan!
- Are we off today?
We're going to practice
our dancing from now.
- Want to come along?
- Yes.
On the days the pub is
closed, we practice here.
I'm behind in my dancing
progress, so they're
keeping me company here.
It's doing us good, too.
It's all for our dream.
How many times will this
be for the bar exam?
Twenty-six.
Society only looks
at the end result.
If you are serious about
becoming an attorney,
then show me the results
in the exams next week.
This is your last chance.
Last?
I hope we can pass together.
You look awfully confident.
Those guys!
What are you doing, Satoi?
It's noisy!
This isn't your practice
dancing hall!
Sensei may allow it,
but I won't!
Go elsewhere to dance!
Who thinks Satoi's voice
is more irritating?
It's five against one,
and we win.
Does that vex you?
You want to go to court?
- What's the matter?
- It's irritating.
You have it rough, Satoi.
You have to know
when to give up.
I'm not giving up.
I'm going to pass it.
The words "last chance"
have an awful ring to it.
Don't say that.
Are you confident
you can pass?
Don't ask me that.
- Shinpei, I...
- What's wrong?
Kusunoki, my friend,
got killed.
Killed?
With one gun shut.
They found illegal drugs
in his suit pocket.
The higher-ups think he
was involved in drugs
and was killed as a result.
But he wouldn't get
involved in that.
He was the most earnest
person among my peers.
He was always cheerful.
But wasn't he carrying
the drugs on him?
If there's evidence...
He came to confide
in me yesterday.
But I didn't hear him out.
Then he got killed here.
I want you to investigate
the truth for me.
Or he'll be branded as a
police detective who got
involved in drugs.
He'll lose all his benefits.
When I think about his
family, I don't know
what to do anymore.
I want to believe that
he's innocent.
Is there any witness?
If there is, that person
would be killed, too.
Witness, huh.
Dream, huh.
I should find one, too.
- Marimo-chan!
- Hello!
I'm on my lunch break now.
Would you like to join me?
Sure.
I don't know what to do.
Friendship or love...
I can't choose
between the two.
You're greedy,
aren't you?
What do you mean?
You don't want to be
disliked by your friends,
but you want to go
out with the boy.
Life isn't all that rosy.
What about you then?
What?
You have "him" but you went
out with your former fiancé.
- Did you see that?
- You want to have both, too.
You're not any
different from me.
- Adults have to be tactful.
- Children have circumstances.
Thank you for lunch.
That's true.
What should I do?
Do you know anything
about yesterday's incident?
I was off yesterday.
We don't work at that hour.
Do you know if anyone
was working at that time?
Not that I know of.
Thanks anyway. Let me know
if you remember anything.
I'm sorry to call you out.
Satsuki, I...
It's all right.
I'm over him.
I'm sorry.
He kissed me unexpectedly.
I only dated him for a week.
But it'll still remain
as a good memory to me.
It's all right. It's the
summer. I'll find a new love.
A week?
You only dated him
for a week?
That's not the point,
is it?
I want to remain
as your friend.
I'm fine with it.
I'm sorry.
That hurts! What are
you trying to do?
You're always irate,
aren't you?
That's dangerous. What
if I got hurt from it?
- Aren't you hungry?
- No, I'm not.
Come.
Thank you for waiting.
One gets irritable
when he's hungry.
Don't hold back and eat.
I'm not hungry.
Don't you like gyûdon?
It's delicious.
Wait up.
Kimchi is a must-eat
food in the summer!
It'll give you energy.
I said I'm not hungry!
In that case...
Why can't you offer to
treat me to yakiniku?
- It's expensive.
- Still, offer it to me.
If you're worried
that I'm irritable,
then offer it to me!
Oh, so you're got
the energy now.
When you take an
exam in school...
School?
There's a time limit,
like 30 minutes.
It's 45 minutes.
In a relationship between
a man and a woman...
It's complicated, so there
is no right or wrong answer.
In other words, just tackle
the problem at your own pace.
If you can't resolve it today,
then work on it tomorrow.
And if not tomorrow, then
resolve it down the line.
In short, don't rush and panic.
What are you going
to do about Asami-san?
As an adult, I have ample...
You have a call coming in.
Is that you, Ran?
I'll be right over.
Just take it slowly.
He's trying to act mature.
Drugs?
That's right, drugs.
They say you can get
it for cheap lately.
At 50% off.
I think the boss there
is involved in it.
Who's the boss?
Don't ask me.
- I can find out, though.
- Please find out.
I'm the one who called
earlier. Know anything?
I bet you want information
on yesterday's incident.
That's right. Do you
know anything?
No, we don't.
- Got any?
- Got what?
Drugs.
Don't tell him or you
will get caught.
Which means, you know.
Tell me, will you?
Satoi, go home.
You'll fail again.
Shut up. I don't want
you to worry about me.
You're scared. Go home.
You're in the way.
I'm only being quiet
to let you look good.
I'm better at gathering
information than you.
- You can't do it.
- Yes, I can.
This is the place.
It's hot today.
I don't know anything.
Please try to remember
who was selling drugs lately.
I said I don't know!
Let's leave.
Even a rumor will do.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
- Kitaoka-san!
- What are you doing here?
I'm Kusunoki's peer.
I wanted to deliver his
belongings to his family.
He's under suspicion.
- Don't touch the evidence.
- He's not the type to to that.
I know! I believe him, too!
Just leave it to me.
An answer...
If not today, then tomorrow.
That's true.
There's no use panicking.
Is he a masher?
He looks very scary!
I thought we were off today.
That doesn't tell me
anything!
Don't talk to me like that!
Explain it to me so that
I can understand!
What were you secretly
discussing with Non?
What do you mean
by "fire"?
Who do you plan to fire?
Shut up! I'm going
to decide that from now!
Don't show up on our day
off and eavesdrop!
We overheard it when we
came to get our dancing shoes!
Just don't tell
anyone about it!
Is that clear?
We're going to call everyone
together for a meeting.
Wait a minute!
- Did you hear that?
- I'm sorry.
Will you tell me your opinion?
Who should I fire
from the show staff?
Kikugorô, Jun, Kôji, Ponta,
Mitchi, Chôko, or Sotokoba-san?
Who do you think
I should cut?
Everyone is trying their best.
They were practicing
on their own today.
Who do you think
I should cut?
- They're all trying their best.
- They're trying their best?
What I want is results.
Life isn't that easy that
all it takes is efforts.
What's going on?
One person is going
to get fired.
It's his usual joke again.
I'm not going to lose.
- Same here.
They lack the
competitive spirit.
They're good guys
as you say.
But that, alone, won't
make them survive.
You've lost me.
They're like a group of
old college friends.
They're not pros who are
trying to make a go at it.
Since this is just a pub,
they don't think they'll
ever lose their job.
It's that naivety that will
destroy the talent in them.
But you don't have
to fire them.
I don't want to cut
anyone, too.
But sometimes, it just
has to be done.
We have to get rid of
the rotten apple.
I wonder where Satoi-san is.
If he doesn't study
hard, he'll fail.
If we know who's selling it,
then we can find the culprit.
- What's the matter?
- Nothing.
What a laugh!
You said you were better
at gathering information!
But you were scared
the whole time!
No, I wasn't!
You wanted to leave.
You were trembling.
- How unsightly!
- I realized today...
that sewer rats like you
suit dirty scenes like that!
I'm more fit to delegate.
You're more fit to scramble
in the back alleys.
I'm of attorney calibre.
He's making excuses
for himself.
He's wet his pants.
- You're right.
- No, I haven't!
Go home!
That small penis
of his wet his pants.
No, I haven't! Feel it!
Doesn't he worry or get
jealous over it?
Go home and study.
You're bothering us.
I can't leave after
I hear that.
I am a man, too.
So what're you
going to do?
Is someone being targeted?
There's a strange car outside.
- What's that car?
- They must be killers.
You kept snooping around,
so they sent men after you.
What fools!
I have nothing
to do with this!
So he runs away
at the crucial moment.
Why do you think that
car is suspicious?
Because I saw that
car this afternoon, too.
Wait a minute... Where
did I see it again?
Life isn't all that rosy.
I know, I was with
Marimo-chan.
Is Marimo-chan
being targeted?
Why Marimo?
Manager, you should
tell everyone that.
Then they will try
even harder.
Don't be an idealist.
What's wrong with that?
Adults are always...
Are you going
to support them?
Can you assure
their success in life?
It's my job to teach them
the harsh realities of life!
Manager, you're mean.
Marimo!
It's hardest on the Manager.
Please understand that.
I...
...can't understand it.
- The Manager is just trying to...
- I don't understand it!
Why do you say that?
You're such a kid!
I just don't understand it,
old lady!
- She came out.
- Get her.
Marimo!
What an unfortunate...
- Who are you?
- What is it?
- Non.
Marimo? Why are you there?
Non-san and I were arguing.
Then we were grappling.
Watch out, fool!
Are you serious about it?
I'm sorry.
It looks like your goal is
to take the bar exam and
not to pass it.
- That's not true.
- You needn't come anymore.
Please wait, Sensei.
I'll study diligently.
I'll try my hardest.
I'll definitely pass
the exam next week!
So please don't say that.
Thanks.
Sensei... I think Satoi-san
is trying his best.
What you said earlier...
About not coming to work
until the exam is over?
Unlike you, he lacks focus.
It's being smuggled
in from the Continent.
They're drugs that were
confiscated in the past.
What do you mean?
Someone in the police is
doing illegal channeling.
Who?
Does that have anything to do
with the guys who are after me?
Aren't there too many
people here?
Please tell me more about
the illegal channeling.
So there was a case
like that last night.
The man who was killed
was his friend.
I was in this area last night.
Come to think of it...
Don't tell me the culprits
were in that car.
Did you see the culprits?
Remember what kind
of car it was.
- What color?
- How many were inside?
- Did you see their faces?
- Don't ask all at once.
You're useless.
I didn't think it was
the culprits' car.
How would I remember it?
It was only yesterday.
Try to remember it.
I'm trying to remember.
What kind of memory
do you have?
Shut up!
Can't you remember
anything?
Will you be quiet for a bit?
If it's the car that was
parked out there earlier...
Do you remember the
license number of that car?
What about you?
You should talk!
You were looking at it
as the culprits' car!
That only happened less
than an hour ago!
What kind of memory
do you have?
Sorry.
How can you be a private
detective at that?
- Don't tell me that.
- The car... was a sedan.
Is that the car that
passed me earlier?
Then the color was navy blue.
The license plate read
"Shinagawa..."
The number is...
Did you call me
an old lady?
Marimo!
I remember!
Who is she?
I don't know.
She just showed up in my car.
Like an illusion.
We'll just have to kill her.
I found out the owner
of the car.
Kitaoka Shûzô, who lives
in Setagaya-ku...
Wait a minute.
Kitaoka Shûzô is my superior.
Your superior?
Now, now. So he's the culprit?
What's going on?
The one who should be
cracking down on drugs
is being taken in by the
drugs and is selling them
to the fools for want
of money.
Kusunoki's lips were
sealed because he found out.
How dirty.
- That's terrible.
- We should notify the police.
Please wait.
I don't want to believe that.
He's trying his best to prove
that Kusunoki is innocent.
I believe him, too!
He's the superior that
I respect most.
He would never do that.
What do we do?
Let's give him time
to think things over.
What are you saying?
Don't be convinced.
He's troubled right now.
Wasn't your friend killed?
I don't know how he was
in the past, but...
He's the bad guy now.
He's a villain.
Don't sympathize with him.
The Manager is having it
hard, too.
He's worried about
all of you.
He's troubled and sad of
having to fire someone.
- What're you talking about?
- Fire someone?
That's what it means
to be an adult.
Adults are sly!
You want to clear your
friend's name,
but you want to believe
in your superior.
What's bad is bad.
There is only one answer.
Non-san is in danger.
Is that right?
Is that what he said?
It's hopeless for me.
Not after he went that far.
- Cheer up.
- I have the fighting spirit.
But I get too nervous
during the exams.
So I can't show the results.
Shall we go somewhere dark?
- Where?
- Here.
There's a group out there.
Are they the guards?
- What are we going to do?
- I'll call for aid. Wait.
- We can't be waiting.
- They're real yakuza.
We'll stand no chance
against them.
We just have to storm in.
What is it?
- What are you doing?
- Practice.
We were going to practice
one last time so that we
won't have regrets when
one of us is fired.
I wasn't invited.
What are you doing here?
Kitaoka-san!
Do you realize what
you are doing?
I only meant to do it once!
Why did you kill Kusunoki?
When did you turn that way?
Aren't you a police detective?
What happened to your
initial spirit?
I don't know what happened
myself! Before I knew it...
I was selling the drugs
that I had confiscated.
The money kept pouring
in so I couldn't stop.
There is only one answer.
What's bad is bad.
Then Kusunoki found out, so...
You're trash.
Please let me go.
Get real!
Are you all right?
Why do people change?
The greed in you
grows with age.
Be it money, status,
women, or wealth.
They're greedy fools.
Are you the same?
I don't understand adults.
I got something that
I didn't want.
You're the worst.
Greedy fools?
Falling in love with your
friend's boyfriend is the
- start of greed, too.
- He's her ex-boyfriend.
Hey, lady!
Shinpei-san?
You must want more.
Not today, though.
- I have a schedule, too.
- Do you know each other?
The other day, we...
Is he the one you love?
Why are you blushing?
What's your relationship
to each other?
Father and daughter.
Isn't that a surprise?
- She's my daughter.
- How do you know each other?
The other day, we...
Did you see anybody
you like?
Her!
You have good taste.
- Don't tell her.
- Of course.
Something seems suspicious.
Go on a date with him.
To the karaoke box or club.
Or even a love hotel.
Hey!
- Enjoy yourselves with this.
- I don't want it.
See you later.
He's cool.
How do you know him?
- Let's go.
- Where?
To the karaoke box.
Or maybe the club.
Or maybe to the hotel.
Hey!
He's aggressive.
God, is this my reward for
trying so hard today?
Is this for real?
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
MATSUNAGA YÔICHI
A Production of
JOKER & TBS
2014-10