They're having an
erotic conversation.
Open the curtains
and show me your faces.
When I found out that he was
my papa, I wanted to die.
But lately, I've been
thinking that he's not
all that bad.
Shinpei, I brought
you food.
Thanks.
What is it?
It matches you.
You look great.
Think so?
You look good, too.
Do I look like the
typical private eye?
You do. You sure do.
You have to be tough
to survive in this world.
You have to be kind or
you don't deserve to live.
Where were you yesterday?
I don't remember.
It's too long ago.
Can I see you tomorrow?
That's too far in the
future to...
The curtains are open!
We've got the scandal on
bureaucrat Munakata's wife!
This completes the job!
I don't see any attractive
guys around.
All the good ones
are already taken.
Satsuki, what are you saying?
You have Rintarô-senpai.
Rintarô is in love
with someone else.
- Is that right?
- So we broke up.
I've fallen in love
with you.
That's terrible!
That's so rude!
Marimo? Your cell
phone is ringing.
It's me, Rintarô.
I want to see you once more.
When you slapped me in the
face with all your might,
it got me thinking.
I want to talk it out
with you.
But...
What is it?
Come out!
Let's see the dirty
exposures.
Is that you, Marimo?
Don't open this door. I'm
developing pictures now.
OK.
What should I do?
They're developed.
Do you want to see them?
It's Kirishima Detective
Office's first job.
They have a love triangle
going on here.
She's having an affair
with her friend's husband.
She's a wretch for doing
such an immoral thing.
I know you can't stop love,
but you have to learn how
to control your feelings.
Don't ever become like her.
Why do you tell me that?
Didn't you just
get defensive?
Are you stupid?
I wouldn't do such a thing!
You must be doing
something immoral!
The photos are disgusting!
What are you saying?
This is my job!
- Something smells.
- Get out!
He's sharp. He's seen
right through me.
I have to control my
feelings or I'm a wretch?
Is this any summer
for a 17-year-old?
HITONATSU NO PAPA E
MATSUSHIGE YUTAKA
KITAGAWA HIROMI
TSUGUMI
MATSUDA SATOSHI
ICHIHARA HAYATO
KOBAYASHI CHIHARU
YAMANAKA SÔ
KINBARA YASUNARI
TSUNOMURA MAKO
TOYOKAWA EIJUN
HIRANUMA NORIHISA
SAKAI MASATO
HAYASHI YASUFUMI
KOBAYASHI MIKA
SAWAJIRI ERIKA
USUDA ASAMI
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
Directed by
HIROKI YÛICHI
EPISODE 5:
SHINU NA! ORE GA
ZETTAI TASUKETE YARU...
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
- You've reached Shinpei.
- Shinpei, tonight...
Kirishima Detective Office
is out on a job right now.
Murderer.
Doctor, you shouldn't
be drinking so recklessly.
You're an adult.
Drink it more slowly.
- Sorry I'm not young.
- I didn't mean it that way.
Have you ever killed
someone before?
What?
That shut you up, didn't it?
Here, have a drink.
Here, eat.
Dr. Asami seems a bit
reckless in her drinking.
Maybe she's having
problems with her man.
Stupid. She must've had
a bad surgical experience.
She gets out of hand
when she's drunk.
- What happens?
- Well...
She kept us here till
morning the other time.
Till morning?
She even danced.
- She must be passionate.
- She danced the Latin.
Dr. Asami's great, isn't she?
She's pretty, smart,
and competent.
I want to be like her.
- She's the "dondon" type.
- What's a "dondon"?
She must've been good
at handling the men.
She seems to have
dated a lot of men.
She probably got every
man she wanted.
- She's the queen of love.
- "The queen of love"?
Maybe I'll ask her.
It feels good to work
for yourself.
It makes you feel
like a king.
Marathon runners
are awesome.
You don't see anyone griping
when they're running.
What brought that on?
You don't see anyone behind
them griping either.
Only the ones that retire
along the way make excuses.
Shinpei, don't become
one of the losers now.
You've started running.
So grit your teeth.
OK!
Let's make a toast.
Do you really
understand what I mean?
Good night!
Hi.
- Are you running?
- Huh?
Are you gritting your teeth?
You should get a good
grip of the ground.
You sure like to pick
fights with me.
- Don't you like me?
- Good night!
- Marimo!
- What is it?
I got a picture of your
ugly face.
Did I look ugly?
Give it back to me!
It's my face you took!
No!
You can't just take my
photo without permission!
- Are you gritting your teeth?
- You're not making sense.
- Where were you yesterday?
- It's none of your business.
- Will you see me tomorrow?
- I see you everyday.
- Do you like me?
- What about you?
Of course I like you.
- In fact, I love you a lot.
- More than Asami-san?
You're too realistic.
Got you there.
I'm going out for more drinks.
He makes me tired.
Latin dancing...
Queen of love...
I want to see you again
and talk it out.
I'm in a bind.
But... she might laugh if I
confide in her about this.
Is that right?
So you're brooding.
Is it over a man?
- It's summer now.
- Can you tell?
And the boy you like
is your friend's boyfriend.
Can you tell that, too?
- Did I get that right?
- So you were just guessing.
Will you tell me about it?
I'll be your confidante.
- It's really nothing.
- Hey! Tell me!
- Never mind!
- Why?
Never mind! It's nothing!
Done!
Perfect!
We just have to deliver
this to the client and
we get paid a million yen!
I'm so happy!
Hey!
Satoi-mo!
Looks like you're having fun.
This is a present for
your grand opening.
Satoi, will you bring
something better?
That's awfully blunt.
Well, it's from the
confidence I've gained.
Maybe it's the money.
Money? Don't get
carried away by it, fool.
We earned a million
yen in three days.
- Seriously?
- Wow!
I'm going to buy us a melon
instead of a watermelon.
Get a Yûbari melon.
So you said, you want
to eat a Yûbari melon.
And I don't blame you.
I'm going out to get it.
I don't follow.
You want us to search
for your former lover?
She's our secretary.
And what are you
going to do?
- Do I have to tell you that?
- Well...
We want to make sure we're
not lending a hand in a crime.
That's right.
I want to ask her
to marry me.
So you're out to get her.
- The name first.
- Utsunomiya Shun'ichi.
- Not your name. Hers.
- Don't be nervous. Relax.
Inoue Asami.
Inoue Asami?
We were engaged before.
But we broke up because
of "that" incident.
What incident?
I realized how precious
she is, only now.
Is something wrong?
What happened with her?
- I'm curious, too.
- Please tell us.
I have a headache.
I drank too much.
I don't believe this.
- Good morning.
- Good morning?
Isn't is a surprise?
Nothing happened, right?
You got that, right?
We have our clothes on.
I spent the night out
without telling my wife.
What am I going to do?
Wait!
Don't tell anybody
about this now.
Of course! I have a
family that I love!
What is that
supposed to mean?
Is that what's going
on between you two?
Is that right?
Adults have a lot of
secrets. Scary!
It's not what you think.
It's a misunderstanding.
It's really not what
you think.
So you're both
defending each other?
Is that right?
I said you've got it
wrong, damn hag!
Damn hag?
Hey! What was that?
You're getting paid
with our tax money!
What did you just say?
It's really not what
you think.
You'll do.
I'm going to confide
in you.
Please help me with
my love problem.
Detective office?
Is this where she lives?
I'm going in.
What are you doing?
- Hello.
- Hi.
- What a surprise!
- Dr. Asami's former fiancé?
It's a problem, isn't it?
Should we tell Asami-chan
about it or not?
I said you should tell her.
If she finds out that
he's looking for her,
she might get
married to him.
- Then let her.
- Then Shinpei-san will be jilted.
Oh, I see.
- That's true.
- It's truly a problem.
Why did he break up with
Dr. Asami in the first place?
Weren't you listening to
what happened in the past?
No.
Then don't join in on
the discussion.
He's actually my
friend's boyfriend.
To be accurate, he's
my friend's ex-boyfriend.
- The one who kissed you?
- Yes.
You seem to have a lot of
experience in these things,
so I came to seek your advice.
It happened when she was
at the university hospital.
They had many emergencies
that particular night.
Excuse me. We have a request
to take an emergency patient.
A boy had fallen down the
stairs and hit his head.
Turn him away.
Take him.
And that emergency patient
was brought in.
Yûji!
I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to save him.
I'm very sorry.
Why did you say that?
He'll think that the hospital
made an inappropriate treatment.
A child passed away.
Don't talk about appearances
to me right now.
The hospital was sued by
Ishikura, the patient's family.
So Dr. Asami was forced
to assume the entire blame
- and was dismissed.
- That's awful!
So their engagement was
naturally called off.
That's harsh.
Why is he looking for her
only now?
He realized that he loved
Dr. Asami very deeply.
Then you shouldn't
tell her about it.
Stupid!
You just said she should
be told.
Shinpei is doing fine now
with his own business!
Having a rival like him
pop up now...
Don't talk like you know it
all, divorcée!
- What was that?
- She should be told!
Do I tell her?
If you love him, you
should tell her the truth.
- But he's Satsuki's ex-boyfriend.
- I told my friend's boyfriend.
- Not ex-boyfriend, but boyfriend?
- And I even went steady with him.
- What?
- That's what love is all about.
You knew that he was your
friend's boyfriend, but
you couldn't stop the way
you fell, right?
You didn't think you would
do such a thing,
- but your heart was moved?
- That's right.
- What is it?
- You're experiencing real love.
Do you think so?
Friendship is important,
but so is love.
I feel encouraged, talking
to you.
You have a nice smile.
You should turn off your cell
phone in a restaurant.
Shall we go?
I'll be at the clinic.
Murderer.
Hello? Kumiko?
What's up?
I heard Rintarô-senpai is
in love with you.
That's what he told Satsuki.
I'm really sorry. I've
fallen in love with Marimo.
Is that right?
Don't act dumb.
Didn't you kiss him?
It's not what you think.
Are you going to choose
friendship or love?
Friendship, of course.
Can you tell that to Satsuki?
Of course.
We'll be waiting at Daisan
Park at 3:00.
I don't believe this.
I should choose friendship,
after all.
Asami-san is different.
I can't tell Satsuki I want
to be with Rintarô.
Asami-san, I'm going.
- Marimo-chan, run!
- What?
You're terrible. Bringing
that cute kid here.
He's a bad boy. He was
loitering in front of my office.
I thought he'd do better
with someone closer to his age.
How cute! So you're worried.
It's better to get it off
his chest.
Refer him to someone good.
It would be great to have
a papa like you.
Don't you think so?
I think so myself.
But Marimo just doesn't
get it.
Did you see anybody
you like?
Her!
You have good taste.
I feel refreshed!
Is the next customer here?
I'll be leaving now.
- Nasty.
- Do you know each other?
- You dirty old man.
- Hoshino-san is a regular.
- Is that right?
- It's not what you think.
I stayed out all night,
so my wife won't let me
into the house.
No wonder your daughter
went delinquent.
When I woke up, it was
already morning.
You're a bad officer.
I sweated a bit so I came
here to take a shower.
Go to a bathhouse.
I was shocked to wake up
next to Dr. Asami.
- Too bad nothing happened.
- Did you just say, "Asami"?
- Did you sleep with Asami?
- I have such loose lips.
Damn you!
How could you sleep with
my Asami!
You hit an officer three times.
I'm not talking to you anymore!
We shouldn't let
Shinpei-san know.
- He'll be bedridden.
- We should tell him.
That's only natural.
It's a job.
Don't let personal feelings
influence your work.
But it can't be avoided
in this particular case.
It's that kind of attitude
of yours that makes you
incompetent at work
and in your dancing.
Why is he so cocky?
I'm sorry. He just acts
big to people he knows.
- He has a cold heart.
- Freezing cold!
You must not be well-liked.
There are things that
you shouldn't say.
Sato-imo!
I'm going to sue you
for slander!
- Where's Shinpei?
- What's wrong?
Marimo-chan's
been kidnapped.
What? Marimo?
I'll check to see if he's
in his room.
- Darn...
- Excuse me.
I have nothing to do
with this, do I?
Shut up!
Shinpei-san isn't back yet.
He's not answering his
cell phone, either.
- What is that fool doing?
- I'm going to look for him.
Do you know where he is?
If you don't, don't run
about aimlessly!
It won't do us any good
to stay here.
Call the police!
But what if Dr. Asami's
past comes to light?
What is she loses clients?
I'm going to check all
the places he may be.
Me, too.
Manager, stay here and
watch the place.
Be careful.
Dr. Asami, stay here.
He's not here.
- Did you find him?
- Where did everyone go?
Let's have faith in everyone.
I'm sure Shinpei will
come through.
- Satoi-san?
- I'm going out.
Shinpei-san,
don't misunderstand.
Nothing happened.
- Go away, pervert cop!
- Don't say that.
Shinpei!
I have something to tell
you about this pervert cop.
Come with me.
Hurry.
Damn!
I...
What is it?
I have to meet Satsuki and
Kumiko at 3:00.
Shut up. Are you in any
position to be saying that?
Don't take me lightly!
Why? Why is that woman
practicing medicine?
She killed my child!
How can she continue?
I heard the details
from Satoi.
Shinpei, I'm sorry to pull
her into this.
- Where does he live?
- He wasn't at home.
Ishikura got a divorce
earlier this year because
of the constant bickering
he had with his wife after
their child died. And
he's unemployed.
He's trying to get
revenge on Asami.
The police think so, too.
Police? Did you go to
the police?
- I told him to.
- Why did you do that?
Marimo-chan's life is on the
line here!
Marimo!
Is that you, Ishikura?
- Please return Marimo.
- Is Inoue Asami there?
- She's not here.
- No!
What are you doing?
Tell her that she killed
my son.
I'll let her have a taste
of what I suffered.
The pain of losing
a loved one.
This is Inoue. Marimo-chan has
nothing to do with this.
Please let her go.
Shut up! I'll kill your
friends one at a time.
I don't want to die.
Ishikura-san, please stop.
Then kill yourself and
make amends!
Die in a grand manner and
make tomorrow's news!
Can you do that?
You cut me.
- You really cut me!
- Marimo-chan!
Ishikura! What did you do
to Marimo!? I'll kill you!
- Calm down!
- Let me hear Marimo's voice!
- Let me hear her voice!
Do you know who you are
talking to?
Shut up, fool!
Let me hear her voice!
Don't yell into the receiver!
I'll let you hear her voice.
Remember her words well.
Hello?
- Marimo? Are you OK?
- He cut my face.
If I'm unpopular, it'll
be your fault.
Where are you?
I don't want to die.
Don't worry. I promise
I'll save you.
Everyone has unlucky days.
But this is the worst day
for me.
Mama died.
Then you became my papa.
When I found out you were
my papa, it was the pits.
But today is even worse.
Never mind that. Where
are you now?
- Near Mama.
- What?
When you're sad...
Why do you want to be
with the ones you love?
Shinpei!
Ishikura!
Hurry and find her, Satoi!
Marimo-chan's life
is on the line!
Where are you now?
OK!
Marimo-chan is somewhere
around here.
Was that your dad?
He suddenly shows up
in my life.
We've only been together
for a month.
But we're trying our best
to be father and daughter.
He sounded desperate.
What?
He really did.
Hang in there!
Yûji!
Please save him!
I was desperate, too...
that night.
But he didn't make it.
Yûji!
I know I'm wrong for
hating the doctor.
But I was working till
late every night,
and I couldn't even play
with him on my days off.
Then I lost my job.
I didn't do anything for
Yûji for seven years.
Marimo!
- You pervert!
- Stay away!
How dare you cut her face!
As a parent, you should
know how I feel!
Why did you hurt my Marimo?
Don't beat around the bush!
"When you're sad, you want to
be near your loved ones."
Just say that you're by
his son's grave.
- I really had to think about that.
- So you figured out.
Well, she couldn't just
come out and say it!
- Isn't that right, Marimo-chan?
- Did you set me up?
I don't want to die.
Ishikura-san!
His chance of survival
was only 0.1%.
But I didn't want to give
up on him.
It wasn't as if it was
completely hopeless!
I really wanted to save him!
Ishikura-san, I can't die.
I won't stop practicing.
I want to save as many
people as possible.
So I can't do as you say.
Doctor...
I'm sorry.
- What are you doing?
- Ishikura-san!
This should do it.
Are you all right?
It was pretty tiring.
For you.
- It's a Yûbari melon.
- Thanks.
I've never seen you like that.
You were desperate.
I have to be serious
sometimes.
If I ever get taken
as a hostage,
will you save me with
a serious look like that?
What is it?
It's you, isn't it?
Of course.
It must've been scary.
While you can still feel
the pain, you're fine.
Pain is the hope in life.
When you stop feeling pain,
then you're over the edge.
What a shock. That's what
my mama used to say.
She was a nurse and she used
to tell her patients that.
I heard it from a certain
nurse myself.
You're stealing her line then.
Do you feel pain?
I was just thinking...
What is my hope?
I was afraid of being tied up.
I was afraid of being hurt.
I was afraid of everything.
Maybe I had faith...
...that he would come
to save me.
That's father and daughter
for you.
He's more like a friend to me.
That'll heal in no time.
You took too long.
What are you saying?
My timing was perfect.
If it leaves a scar, I'm
going to sue you.
Don't worry, it'll go away.
How is he doing?
He's going to the police
hospital.
- This is for you.
- Thanks.
- What about me?
- Don't be tight.
Who's that?
Asami-chan's former fiancé.
Fiancé?
Poor thing.
- Hi.
- I don't believe it.
Why didn't you come?
Oh, that's right! I'm sorry.
Rintarô?
It was pure coincidence.
- Is that what's going on?
- No, it's not what you think!
Will a love that started
at the bottom of the sea
disappear with the foam of
the sea or turn into the
blazing summer sun? We're
having a love scramble tonight.
My summer was definitely
moving forward.
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
HIROKI YÛICHI
A Production of
JOKER & TBS
2014-10