What's going
to happen to Marimo?
She can't stay with me.
I have no spare room.
Can she stay at the
dorm for a while more?
By policy, I can't allow a
person without a guardian,
that's a high school
student, live there.
Are you going to kick
her out then?
Don't put it like that!
Wait!
MOCHIZUKI FAMILY GRAVE
Stop the music!
Sotokoba-san!
- Why don't you quit?
- What?
Why don't you quit this job?
Now, now.
You're slowing
down everyone.
Stop smiling!
Put your all into it!
Excuse me.
Lunch hour is over.
What?
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
Everyone is...
- Excuse me.
- What is it?
Well... I'm...
I don't believe this!
Shinpei-san!
Shinpei has a daughter?
KONARI LAW OFFICE
Sensei!
Where's Sensei?
Knock before you come in!
Have you no manners!
Is Sensei around?
Don't visit him like a friend.
He's a busy man.
And he's too expensive for
you to afford for counseling.
- Leave!
- That hurts!
You're aggravating me, Satoi.
- Not Satoi-san?
- You're younger than me.
I have a better paying
job than you.
You're just a part-timer
like me.
You can't even get
your law license.
You've got the gall!
Out of my way!
Sensei!
You're making
too much noise.
Do you know
where Shinpei is?
He's probably at the rooftop.
Excuse me.
Shinpei!
Why don't you
get a tan with me?
The girls will like it.
Your daughter is here.
What?
Your daughter.
Daughter?
- How old are you?
- Seventeen.
Are you a junior
in high school?
Senior.
Are you really
Shinpei's daughter?
I guess you are.
You wouldn't come
here as a joke.
What's your name?
Mochizuki Marimo.
She has a different
last name as Shinpei.
Must be serious.
What else can it be?
Here.
My mama passed away
two weeks ago.
See! I was right!
What kind of person
is Kirishima Shinpei-san?
Well...
- Married?
- Asking me?
- Why would I ask you?
- He's not.
He's a bachelor.
She's curious about him.
What does he do?
Well... I guess you could
say he's a private eye.
Private eye...
That sound neat.
- He's here.
- Shinpei-san!
Shinpei, she's your daughter.
Her name is Marimo-chan.
My daughter?
You can't be serious.
It came as a big surprise.
My daughter?
Are you my daughter?
That's harsh.
What?
That's a harsh joke.
Shinpei, what are you doing?
What bar are you from?
That hurts!
Don't take me lightly!
HITONATSU NO PAPA E
MATSUSHIGE YUTAKA
KITAGAWA HIROMI
TSUGUMI
MATSUDA SATOSHI
KOBAYASHI CHIHARU
YAMANAKA SÔ
KINBARA YASUNARI
TOYOKAWA EIJUN
TSUNOMURA MAKO
HIRANUMA NORIHISA
SAWAJIRI ERIKA
USUDA ASAMI
KOIDE YUKA
TAKEHATSU SHIRÔ
ICHITANI MAYUMI
ITÔ DAIKI
SUZUKI NAHO
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
Directed by
HIROKI RYÛICHI
EPISODE 1:
TAIYÔ WA NAITE IRU
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Who's this?
He's suing our client,
Dai-Nippon Keizai Shôkô Gaisha.
Tanigawa Ichirô, 41.
He's suing for
wrongful dismissal.
Oh, it's a case of an
unjustified resentment.
It's a pending lawsuit.
He has a high chance
of winning now.
The company who fired
him will then lose face.
Then he had a justified case.
President Kusunoki thought
Tanigawa in accounting
found out about his illegal
dealings so he fired him.
Is that what he was doing
behind the scenes?
But Tanigawa knew
nothing about it.
He doesn't understand
why he was fired.
He's suing to save his pride.
And it all started with the
president's misunderstanding.
But we can't afford to lose.
That's true.
Shut up! Stop making
comments in between.
What's with your attitude?
Stop acting like a smarty pants.
Just find out his weakness.
That should be easy. Go.
Don't order me around.
It's noisy.
Welcome back.
Shinpei.
What did you find out?
Have a seat.
She's who she claims to be.
Do you remember
Mochizuki Yukino?
The nurse that tended to you
when you were taken to the
hospital at age 21,
for an injury in a fight.
She's your daughter
from that time.
Are you serious?
In case something happened
to her, she left your name.
Just accept it already.
- Give me a break.
- My sympathies.
Your past has caught
up to you.
Get to work.
You have to work hard
for your child.
When you get the job
done, I'll pay you.
Not like you're paying me!
Tanigawa Ichirô...
Nakano 7-chôme, Nakano-ku...
It's nearby.
Open quickly...
Where is it?
Where's the public
document?
Yukino...
What are you doing?
Don't scare me like that!
How did you get in?
Get out!
The door was open.
Just get out!
That hurts!
I'm not going to register
you as my daughter!
Another thing...
I don't have money!
I can refer you to a
part-time job, though.
The door was open!
It really was!
How is it?
What do you mean?
Let's just accept reality.
We can't live together.
You wouldn't want that,
anyway, would you?
I may be able to provide
some financial support,
but not entirely.
In other words, you...
Don't say "you."
I have a name. Marimo.
You're such a sassy kid.
This is stupid.
To think you're my papa.
Why am I your daughter?
Not like I wanted to be
your father!
How can you say that
in my face!
Mama, he's the worst.
You have no eye for men.
What father would
kiss his daughter!
It's normal in America.
Aren't you Japanese?
I'm actually an American.
- And you're poor.
- You know...
You said you didn't
have any money.
- That is because...
- You seem loose with women.
What do you expect?
I'm a bachelor.
- You seem unintelligent, too.
- You got that right!
And you look scary.
I took after my mother.
Get off my case.
I want to see Grandma.
- Go to Heaven!
- What about Grandpa?
- He's somewhere.
- What kind of answer is that?
He left us when I was
four years old.
Just like me, then.
What is it?
I won.
TANIGAWA
Papa, are you done?
If you're not going to eat,
I want to clean up.
Just forget about the lawsuit.
Will you go out and work?
Will you bring home money?
Will you provide for us?
I know. But I'm having
a battle of my life now.
Why do you bother with that?
So what if you're fired?
Let the past go.
Face reality.
Work for your family!
Family, huh.
Forget this.
I'm calling it a night.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Is that how it should be?
OK, OK. I'll drink, too.
I'll have another.
Why do I have a kid
when I'm a bachelor?
I don't understand it.
So I want to be
with you tonight.
I want to go to your
place tonight.
You really didn't know?
That you had a child?
Of course I didn't.
She must've really loved you.
Thanks for waiting!
My daughter yelled,
"Damn old man!" to me.
She's at a defiant age,
isn't she?
I'm busy right now.
But I can't tell her
anything back.
Should I leave things
the way they are?
Don't ask me those things.
You're cold, Manager.
Welcome.
Who's that customer?
Don't you know him?
No.
Welcome!
Welcome, Dr. Asami.
Did that call bother you?
Not really.
You don't normally come
during lunch hours.
I had a complex surgery
this morning.
So I had a craving
to eat beef.
That girl there, is
Shinpei's daughter.
She's working here
part-time from today.
She looks like a nice girl.
Is she really his daughter?
She must've taken
after her mother.
True.
Does it bother you, after all?
Why should it?
Did it sway you feelings?
You're awful.
Dr. Asami is here for lunch.
It's hot!
All the customers are gone.
Let's eat!
Itadakimasu!
Eat up!
I want to eat, too!
I'm deducting it
from your pay!
Those three work elsewhere
during the mornings and
come to our lessons
during the afternoons.
Didn't you see us
practicing yesterday?
This place turns into
a show pub at nights.
We are rising stars.
That's so cool!
Think so?
Do you dance, too?
Don't I look like I do?
Well...
Don't say it.
I'll keep working at it.
Marimo, can you dance?
Dance with us.
I can teach you.
I can't dance. I really can't.
Deliver these
to Konari-san's office.
Who's Konari-san?
Our attorney.
We pay his retainer fees
with our bentô.
I'm here with the bentô!
Please leave them there.
Are you working hard?
Is she your kid?
Kid?
She's cute!
So she's the one.
I pity you for having
a father like him.
Get back to work.
Be sure to take care of her.
You have to, by law.
It's your duty to provide her
with a home and education.
Satoi.
Are you Marimo-chan?
Feel free to come to me
for help any time.
Hey!
Don't ever talk to that
stupid Satoi again.
He's dumb, but he likes
to talk about education
and social status.
He should come to terms
with his stupidity.
What do you do there?
Work.
Aren't you a private eye?
You're too naive!
The attorneys need
someone like me.
In fact, I'm the one who
supports their livelihood.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
I wonder about that.
It's true. Very true.
Stop crying.
I'm sorry.
Come here.
Come here!
I said to come here!
What? Is she ordering
me around?
So you're Shinpei-chan's daughter.
I'm having a hard time
believing it, too.
I see. Is that right?
Is that good?
Yes.
I see, I see, I see.
What is he like?
You don't refer to him
as your papa?
Oh, I see. I don't blame you.
It's hard to call him papa
out of the blue.
I see.
I think he's a good man.
I like his character.
He must really love people.
He's hungry for family love.
He lost his mother and
siblings in an auto accident.
What do you call it?
I think it's that... that...
You're not aiming right.
He's truly aggravating.
Shinpei!
What's the favor
you want to ask me?
Will you use your
charms to seduce him?
He looks earnest.
He looks delicious.
You don't want to be seen.
Don't forget to collect
5,000 or 10,000 yen from him.
Is it only for 5,000 yen?
No. I'll reward you
generously later.
Don't take photos of
my face with that.
Hello.
Yes?
This is the sign.
What a relief. You look
like an earnest person.
Excuse me, but...
Who's that?
How about this much?
As I said on the phone,
please help me financially.
20,000 yen?
She's a real hooker.
I don't believe this!
They're here.
This is the place.
Let's go in.
Go in!
Don't worry.
Would you like to do
a part-time job?
I'm home!
I need to get her name...
It's Sakuragi Erika-chan.
She's a very bad girl.
Hi.
You're in a good mood.
You're giving me the creeps.
Didn't you call me
a good-for-nothing?
Shall I treat you
to something?
Do you want to eat
sukiyaki or shabu-shabu?
Old man Konari is going
to pay me well for these.
How did you get these?
She did something bad.
Paid companionship.
Give them back to me.
Hey, wait!
What are you going
to do with them?
Beats me.
What kind of answer
is that?
This is my job.
The rest will be up
to old man Konari.
Do you need those
photos for the trail?
Of course.
Shinpei!
I found out her name.
Did you find out which
school she attends?
Yes, I did.
She's a high school student.
Cheese!
Knock before you come in!
- Stop getting jittery.
- He has a small penis.
Stop being vulgar.
What do you want?
- The job's done.
- Is that true?
- See for yourself.
- He's going into a hotel.
- Who is this woman?
- A paid companion.
If you blackmail him with
this, he'll back down.
His wife is scary.
This is too good to be
true, coming from you.
That was uncalled-for.
If you're going to say that,
I can always tear them up.
Stop it.
Just kidding!
Are you stupid? Why
would I tear them up?
They're going to
change into money.
Are you feeling jittery again?
Stop it.
I forgot to report this
to the Sensei.
What do you think of this?
A paid companion.
Perfect.
Wouldn't that
intimidate Tanigawa?
Sakuragi Erika-chan, age 17.
A senior at Teito High School.
Is she a high school student?
She's been doing it for
a while through a circle.
Her father is a Section
Chief of a major bank,
and her mother is a
full-time housewife.
This should get him
to back down.
Can I get paid for it?
Stop it.
So this is your job...
This is what you
do for a living.
What're you getting at?
You investigate on the
person's private lifestyle
and you make
a living off of that.
Is that what you were
going to treat me with?
I'm sorry. She's still a kid.
Why didn't you stop the
crime before it happened?
What?
She went to the hotel
with a stranger.
If he was a whacko,
she could've been killed.
So why didn't you stop
them before they went in?
Is she your friend?
She has nothing
to do with us.
Nothing to do with you?
That's right. I just
did my job.
It doesn't matter to me
what happens to the person.
Oh yes, it does! You
were there watching it!
What have I done that
deserves your criticism?
- Am I wrong?
- You're not wrong at all.
It's your friend and that
man that are wrong.
If you have time to take
photos, then stop them.
Why should I?
A woman who wants money.
A man who buys her with money.
They're both doing it
at their free will.
They're in agreement
with each other.
It's not my business
if Tanigawa kills Erika.
You're the worst.
You know...
What do you think
you're doing!?
Now you've got me mad!
Don't show up out of the
blue and criticize my work!
You're an eyesore!
Screw you!
Hey!
Don't have
expectations of me.
I'm not like that.
There's always "that"
possibility for a girl.
A child like me, who didn't
know of her papa, can be born.
You're a scum to society.
This guarantees our
victory in the lawsuit.
This is the pay for this
job. Give it to Shinpei.
Don't show such a sad smile.
Shinpei! We got paid!
She's so immature.
Deliver the negatives
and photos later.
You know...
I'm not increasing the pay.
I'm dropping out of this one.
What are you saying?
Are you stupid?
Don't be fettered by her.
This is a lucrative job.
You get paid this much
for two days of work.
400,000 yen for two days!
Isn't that a great job?
I don't like the way
you put it.
She's very naive.
She's exactly like Yukino-chan.
Yukino?
Marimo's mother.
She was a caring and
righteous person.
Did you know her?
I defended him eight times
as a public prosecutor and
six times after
I went on my own.
He's the worst.
They were all for self-defense.
He's running hard for
the sake of others.
In the last case
I defended him in...
He tried to save a guy that
was picked on in town.
The guy was a total stranger.
It's not normal, right?
That night, at the hospital
he was rushed to,
he met with Yukino-chan.
He's not legally bound to
take care of Marimo, but
Yukino-chan entrusted Marimo
in Shinpei's care.
Her dearly beloved daughter.
So they aren't real
father and daughter?
I wonder if he'll change...
...after meeting Marimo.
What's wrong?
Satoi-san gave me this.
These are the
negatives and photos.
Please be sure to win
against that Tanigawa guy.
See you later.
What are you doing?
You don't get paid for it.
You didn't do any work.
It was premature work.
So I won't pay you for it.
Shinpei.
What were those tears
for anyway?
Respond to her feelings.
Mama... why did you
leave me alone?
I searched all over for you!
What is it?
I lost my pay because of you.
I'll be straight with you!
I'm not registering you
as my daughter!
What?
I'm not registering you!
What was that?
And I don't have money!
I can't hear you!
You're kidding, right?
I'm serious. Come.
I'm going to scream!
Your friend is in this room.
What?
Fools like her don't learn.
I'll only help this once.
Hello? Shall we get to it?
Let's have fun already.
Stop right there.
Who are you people?
Are you a pervert?
Will you get it going
with her?
I'm going all out today.
I'm ready to shoot.
No!
Don't give us that.
This is what happens
when you get carried away.
Erika.
I forgot something.
Who were those people?
This is for your lesson fee.
You're the worst.
Try resolving it on
your own the next time.
Talk is cheap.
Mama, I want to know...
...the other world that
I don't know of.
I want to know the world
of the man you loved.
Welcome.
Is Shinpei here?
He's over there.
The show is about to start.
We've been waiting for this!
Welcome, everyone!
It's show time again!
We're striving for tomorrow!
Ouch!
Let's make up with a toast.
I'm still a high schooler.
This is summer break.
What kind of parent are you?
That hurts!
When I was on the back
of your bike the other time...
What were you saying?
I said it hurts!
You were clinging close
to me, so I was wondering
- if you had any boobs.
- Don't call it boobs!
Don't touch me!
That hurts!
Stop!
I'm with the police.
Aren't you a high schooler?
For one, you shouldn't
be drinking beer.
But how are you two related?
Can you come with me
to the police station?
It won't take very long.
This is how my 17th
summer had started.
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
HIROKI RYÛICHI
A Production of
JOKER & TBS
2014-08