What are you all doing?
- The typhoon is coming.
- You'll get blown away!
We're working out
to build our stamina.
I bought the protein.
What? Protein?
We all pitched in for it
to get nice muscles.
Aren't you hiding something?
- What's this?
- What is it?
Muscle Museum? Announcing
a new autumn performance?
An emergency audition
due to vacancies?
Are you all trying for it?
Why didn't you tell us
about it? How cold!
Ponta is our rival.
Why would we want
to notify our rival?
What do you mean by that!?
Will you tell me about it!
Wait a minute. Aren't
I considered a rival?
What kind of reaction
is that?
I'm going to pass it
for sure! Just watch!
The high priest was
with Danjiki...
How do I write "danjiki"?
You don't know?
Seriously?
I know how to write it.
I was just testing you.
You don't need to test me
on something that easy.
Shut up. Just cook
breakfast.
That's embarrassing
as a parent.
I said I know how to write it!
Shinpei! They're terrible!
What happened?
Sotokoba-san, I'm sorry.
I won't believe in any
of you anymore.
Let's all take it together.
- Are you sure?
- Let's give it our best shot!
What's going on?
- Thank you for waiting.
- Did you catch a cold?
How unlucky can I be.
I have a date tonight.
Date? I haven't gone
on one for a while.
I don't care what happens
between you and Marimo.
- Please give me your support.
- You and I have a secret.
Did you see anybody
you like?
Her!
You have good taste.
Don't ever tell
Marimo about it.
Women are delicate beings.
If she finds out, you will
definitely be jilted.
So you must keep it a secret.
Are you listening?
Answer me.
Hey!
He looks scary.
What are you talking about?
Don't worry. He's quite
open-minded about life.
Men are wolves.
It's a mystery to me...
Why is he close to
Rintarô-senpai?
Is that the guy that
you like?
you kissed?
Is that the guy that you
stole from your friend?
That doesn't sound nice.
So this handsome lad...
is Marimo-chan's boyfriend.
I've met you once before.
Is the next customer here?
I'll be leaving now.
Why did you like
Marimo-chan better?
What's so good about
that ugly girl?
Are you going on
a date from now?
Please do as I ask.
Was that your daughter?
Is that right?
So your daughter was here.
After I got a divorce two
years ago, I haven't seen.
her in a while.
What did she come here for?
I was shocked myself.
Yôko is getting married.
That's good news!
You had me worried since
you looked so serious.
She's pregnant.
So you're going
to be a grandpa.
That's great! You'll be
a dancing grandpa!
She asked me to change jobs.
What do you mean?
She said although I got
a divorce from her mom,
I am still her dad.
So she wants me
to attend her wedding.
But she wants me to
have a different job title.
She said it won't look
good to have a father that
- is dancing at a pub.
- Is that so?
What's with that? Is she
taking the pub cheaply?
I agree with the Manager.
The title means nothing.
What counts is the heart!
Have confidence in yourself.
- That's right.
- Ignore what she said.
I guess.
The situation is delicate
between a parent and child.
I'll be waiting for your call.
"Danjiki"...
It's summer for you.
Say I want to get married...
And I asked you to change jobs.
What will you do?
Are you referring to what
you heard earlier?
Sotokoba-san looked great.
He was troubled about his
daughter. I was envious.
Stupid. She's taking
her father lightly.
- Think so?
- He has his own life to live.
But she comes along and says
she's pregnant and is getting
married, and she wants to
look good at the wedding,
so she wants him to
change his occupation.
I guess it wouldn't
concern you anyway.
Don't bring up marriage.
Don't think you're sexy
because you have a boyfriend.
I didn't say I was!
Go, quickly. Isn't
he waiting for you?
Now I'm mad.
You needn't come
home tonight.
- Say!
- Ugly.
- You're the worst.
- Ugly!
HITONATSU NO PAPA E
MATSUSHIGE YUTAKA
KITAGAWA HIROMI
TSUGUMI
MATSUDA SATOSHI
ICHIHARA HAYATO
KOBAYASHI CHIHARU
YAMANAKA SÔ
KINBARA YASUNARI
TSUNOMURA MAKO
TOYOKAWA EIJUN
HIRANUMA NORIHISA
YAMAZAKI HAJIME
ASHIKAWA YOSHIMI
MATSUMOTO RIO
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
Directed by
KARAKI AKIHIRO
EPISODE 8:
CHICHI GA NAITE TANON DA
MUSUME NO CHIISANA SHIAWASE
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Summer will be over soon.
Say...
When did you come?
Summer will be over soon.
Do you want a drink?
It's still business hours.
I wonder what Satoi is doing.
Were you serious about him?
Satoi...
That's scary.
I watched the fireworks
with Shinpei last year.
Doctor!
What happened?
It's due to a cold
and exhaustion.
It's nothing serious.
But you can stay and rest.
Thank you.
Be sure to lock up
when you leave.
I have a spare key on me.
Nurse her well.
If Marimo-chan is here, then
Shinpei must be home alone.
Does that mean I'm lucky?
Is that right?
You shouldn't cater
to your child.
Call it love.
It's a parent's love to do
all he can for his child.
That's not right. You
two have both lost it.
My daughter is very defiant.
But I believe that it's
just temporary...
I know how you feel.
I went through that.
- What old men.
- Never mind about that.
We're discussing
Koba-san's job right now
How can you change jobs
so easily because of her?
You're not in your
right state of mind.
A parent has his own life
to live, just as she has
her own life to live.
There's a reason why
you are working there.
- Yes, until this morning.
- Are you serious?
I took off work tonight.
You're going to get
yourself fired.
I'm prepared for it.
This is a father's resolution.
- He's just a stupid father.
- Don't insult him!
She's just trying to get
the count in for the wedding.
After it's done, she'll
forget about you.
There are some things
you shouldn't say!
- Take back the "stupid father"!
- Who cares.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
I'm sorry to spoil
last night.
It's all right. See you.
Is that so? So they had
a hot summer experience.
It's 30 minutes before
opening! Check everything!
Good morning!
Sorry about that. Sotokoba-
chan took the day off.
It's all right. Just pay
me more on the hourly.
OK.
I heard you stayed out.
How do you know that?
The "Is that right?" lady was
telling everyone about it.
"Is that right?"
So you came to see me!
I'm so happy!
- Let's have some fun together.
- I'm not here for that.
What's the urgency?
Your parents are mad?
- I stayed out all night.
- With Marimo?
Are you dating Marimo?
He used to date Marimo's
friend, but now he's
dating Marimo. He has
such weak will.
That's very weak-willed.
I'm not here to talk
about that.
I'm here to talk about
my parents.
I didn't want to cause
you trouble.
- Don't worry about it.
- My parents are very...
All parents talk big.
Don't worry about it.
All my customers
are like that.
I was just getting a list
of those fathers
for my business.
Lad, leave it to me.
Are you sure? No one
likes to do this job?
I'll do anything.
Excuse me... What will
I be doing here?
There's been a lot of
thefts lately.
The security camera
isn't enough.
When the thieves come in,
hit the gasoline cans
and chase them away.
We have a security
alarm, too, but...
This works best.
Do you want the job?
YOTSUBISHI SHÔJI K.K.
Yes, I want it.
The customers by the
door want to see you.
I'm Mochizuki Marimo.
Please have a seat.
- Excuse me...
- I'm Rintarô's father.
Would you like to have
something to drink?
- Iced tea.
- An iced tea for her.
I heard you're Rintarô's
junior in high school.
Are you a senior?
As you know, he's studying
for his entrance exams now.
We can't have him
staying out like last night.
It's an inconvenience.
Don't seduce him.
I'm not.
What college are
you trying for?
I haven't decided.
Are you attending
prep school?
- No.
- Why not?
Because...
What college did your
father graduate from?
I don't think he went
to college.
What does your father do?
He's a private detective.
The one that investigates
on secret love affairs?
I feel like I'm being
interrogated.
You are.
Rintarô's future rests upon
this summer's outcome.
We want to get him into
the college of our choice.
And that's important to us.
He doesn't need to be
distracted by love now.
What does your mother have
to say about the night out?
My mother died of
illness two months ago.
So you only have a father.
A private detective's
daughter?
He's working his hardest.
He's working hard for me.
Why do you put it that way?
Don't you address your
father as your father?
Only after my mama died,
did I find out he's my papa.
And that's when I started
to live with him.
But we are...
He can't be considered
as a father.
Our family environment
is very different from yours.
Our education policies
are different.
Please don't see Rintarô again.
They're awful.
Please don't tell him.
He'll be hurt.
Hey, you two.
You're in a good mood.
I'm supposed to meet
someone for work from now.
We'll make ends meet
this month, too.
Good. Treat me
to something good.
Sure! Just think about
what you want to eat.
- See you later.
- Work hard now!
Bye!
Did you hear that? He's going
to treat me to something good.
I'm going to look forward to it.
See you later.
I'm going to work hard
for my 100,000 yen.
It's pitch dark.
I'm supposed to hit the
cans when the thieves come.
I was shocked.
So there are jobs like this.
Are you happy with this?
Does a parent have
to go that far?
A father who has to work in
the dark warehouse for his
daughter's wedding day.
That's not right, after all.
But I want to attend
her wedding.
A divorce is like abandoning
your duties as a parent.
She has every right
to hate me.
But she came to see me.
And that made me happy.
I want to respond
to her feelings.
I don't understand it.
It's OK for her to be
willful at her wedding.
That's her day to shine.
For that, I would...
That's what it means
to be a parent.
My break is over. I'm going.
Konari-san, it's been
a while.
Marimo?
KONARI LAW OFFICE
She wants to work here?
- Did something happen?
- No.
I get it.
She must like the title of
working for a law firm.
Kids these days can only
think about appearance.
Is it something that you
would cry about?
I'll do anything.
Please hire me.
- What did you say to her?
- I turned her down.
Didn't she ask you to hire
her with tears in her eyes?
As her father,
I'm asking you, too.
If she really wants
to work here, then...
She wants to quit
school and work here.
Quit school?
It's a father's job to earn
money for the family.
But it's also your job
to give her peace of mind.
Do I need this?
What are you doing?
Getting rid of the
things I don't need.
When I moved here, I brought
almost everything with me.
What are you doing?
Don't mess things up.
You need these. These
are your current textbooks.
What are you planning
to do after you quit school?
You're a senior.  You'll
be graduating next year.
It's only a half year more.
- Did you go to college?
- No.
You really don't know
how to write "danjiki"?
You're seriously in trouble.
Shut up. I can earn a living
without knowing that.
So teach me those things.
School is good, too, but...
I thought it'd be better for
me to go out in the real
world as soon as possible.
I wanted to work at
Konari-san's office
and take the bar
exam in my 20's.
And become a lawyer.
Then...
Then I think I will be
acknowledged.
By who?
Society.
So I want to get my
attorney's license.
Let's take a five
minutes break!
Sotokoba-san!
Manager, thank you
for everything.
Hey, wait.
Manager...
What are you saying?
We promised to make
it up together.
Forget about your daughter!
You're not in your
right state of mind.
Don't give up on
your dream for that.
I envy all of you.
You should do what you
want when you're young.
Sotokoba-chan, stay.
It's neat to have an old
man striving hard here.
Some may laugh at it,
but you are the hope of
the middle-aged men.
I can't. My daughter
is more important.
- Damn you!
- Manager?
I was trying to be nice here.
I'm fine. Don't worry.
Stay here!
I'm doing it for Yôko!
Want to go drinking?
I'd love that!
What is it?
You're kind.
I'm always kind.
Shinpei-san!
Don't scare me like that.
I'm sorry!
My parents said some
awful things to Marimo.
- Stay, I said!
- I can't!
I want to do whatever
I can for her as a parent!
What college did your
father graduate from?
What does your father do?
He can't be considered
as a father.
Why?
Why didn't you tell me?
I...
I was upset, too.
I was very upset.
But it's the truth.
Then I just have to
change the truth.
If society will accept
me with that,
then that's fine.
What are you doing!
Let me go!
Let's go home!
I don't think that.
- I told you not to seduce him!
- What are you saying!?
They were both at my
medical clinic yesterday.
Are you a doctor?
Marimo-chan wasn't feeling
well so he was nursing her.
It's true. I told you that.
It doesn't matter. Come.
I don't like what you said.
You hurt Marimo-chan
a lot with your words.
But she asked me to keep
it a secret from her father
- because it'll hurt him.
- Stop it.
I think that if you are
a parent...
I'm worried as a parent!
It's only natural that I worry
about my son's future!
- Who are you?
- Marimo's father.
- So you're the one.
- Apologize to Marimo!
You're a problem.
It's not right for a minor
to work at a place like this.
What do you take your
parental responsibilities as?
That has nothing
to do with it!
- Let me go!
- Shinpei!
Just make a problem of it!
You're the real problem!
Stop interfering into
the kids' affairs!
Stop it!
It's my problem! Drop it!
Just leave me alone.
Let's go home.
A lot of things happen in life.
- I'm sorry.
- You can take off today.
- I'll work.
- Don't force yourself.
I'll just be alone at home.
And I'll feel lonely.
I'm sorry to worry you.
Help us out here.
Let's get back to work!
It's going to be busy tonight.
Rintarô!
Is your husband home?
Excuse me.
What do you think
you are doing?
Shinpei!
Stop!
What do you want?
When you brought up my
parental responsibilities...
- I gave it serious thought.
- How improper can you be!
- Leave!
- I don't know what to do.
- I'm going to call the police!
- Go right ahead!
But please hear me out
until they show up.
Shinpei... What are you
trying to do?
My mother died in
an auto accident.
So I don't know what
child-rearing entails.
I don't know the right
things to do.
I know that I have
to support her.
And I'm trying the
best that I can.
But if that isn't acceptable
by society, then...
That just means that
I'm not good enough.
So please don't think badly
of her because of me.
Leave!
I'll try my best to be
accepted as her father.
I'll even change my job.
I'll find a decent job.
I'll do whatever it takes.
So please don't rob her
of her tiny happiness.
I'm not smart, so this
is all that I can do.
Please!
I'm sure she's feeling screwy
to find out that I'm her father.
But she's trying her best
to be a family with me.
She's even thinking of
quitting school to go to work.
I can't bear to watch that.
Please let her keep
her happiness.
- Leave.
- Please!
- Leave!
- I'm telling you to leave!
- Please...!
Please!
Thanks... for earlier.
And... I'm sorry.
- What do you mean?
- I went too far.
It's rough being a parent.
I should say.
Don't drop out of school.
I'll do all that I can for you.
Pursue your dreams in life.
You can go to college, too.
I'll work hard so send
you through college.
Please don't change.
I don't think badly
of your lifestyle.
Don't say it so seriously.
Especially with that ugly face.
SOTOKOBA
There are good times
and bad times in life.
But if it all balances out,
then that's fine.
Forget all the bad times
you had today, here.
Sweet dreams with this
last performance!
Sagashimono wa
nan desu ka
Mitsukenikui mono
desu ka
Kaban no naka mo
tsukue no naka mo
Sagashita keredo
mitsukaranai noni
Mada mada sagasu
ki desu ka
Sore yori boku to
odorimasen ka
Yume no naka e
yume no naka e
Itte mitai to
omoimasen ka
Sagashimono wa
nan desu ka
Mada mada sagasu
ki desu ka
Yume no naka e
yume no naka e
Itte mitai to
omoimasen ka
It's been two months since
I met with this man, my papa.
He's rough with his words,
but he has a very warm heart.
Yet, I...
Marimo!
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
KARAKI AKIHIRO
A Production of
JOKER & TBS
2014-11