It's hot.
What's all this?
I feel sick.
Will you lock the door!
I don't believe this is
happening from the morning.
What's with you?
You open the bathroom
door then tell me to lock it.
Why should I get yelled at?
You should be the
one to apologize.
Will you lock the door
when you're using it?
Knock first before
you come in.
You came into my room
without knocking first.
How am I supposed
to knock on this?
Don't do to others what you
don't want done to you. Stupid.
Now I'm upset!
Will you be a little
more considerate here?
What's with all these
photos anyway?
I'm at a sensitive age!
These are so disgusting!
Don't leave them here!
They're for my job.
If they're so precious,
store them away somewhere!
- What?
- What is it?
Aren't you conscious?
Isn't this making
you conscious?
Just clear them away!
Then do something
about that.
"That"?
Anybody can see that
we have one too many.
That's what Mama
and I used.
It's using electricity.
As I told you before,
I have no money.
Don't say it so proudly.
But I gave you the money
to go to prep school.
Don't talk big.
But I have every right
to talk big.
Marimo, it's hard
to earn a living.
We can't be wasteful.
You said these photos
are disgusting.
But I'm earning
a living with it.
Will you give it some
serious thought here?
Say...
So you didn't go
to prep school.
Were you planning
to pocket it?
Don't accuse me of that!
I raised the money to
send you to prep school!
- 300,000 yen, too!
- How can I possibly go?
Why not?
If you keep harping
about how poor you are,
how am I supposed
to feel about using it?
Don't act like a person
in poverty.
You're poor and you're
proud of it!
Shut up! You thief!
HITONATSU NO PAPA E
MATSUSHIGE YUTAKA
KITAGAWA HIROMI
TSUGUMI
MATSUDA SATOSHI
KOBAYASHI CHIHARU
YAMANAKA SÔ
KINBARA YASUNARI
TSUNOMURA MAKO
TOYOKAWA EIJUN
HIRANUMA NORIHISA
MR. OKURE
MORISHITA YOSHIYUKI
HADA MIKA
SEKI KEISUKE
HAMAMOTO KÔSUKE
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
Directed by
MATSUNAGA YÔICHI
EPISODE 4:
ANO HITO O SHINJIRU!
KAMISAMA NI CHIKATTE...
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
We can't be wasteful.
Will you give it some
serious thought?
Are you OK?
You looked depressed.
Tell me what's bothering you.
Well...
Why doesn't it come out?
Don't ask me.
You're responsible for the
cash as the cashier!
What's the problem?
The sales isn't matching
the receipts.
We're short by 15,000 yen.
Not that I want to suspect
someone, but I have to.
What do you mean?
Someone here stole it.
I don't know about that.
If you say that...
Why wouldn't it
be possible?
Am I being suspected?
Don't look at me like that.
You and Marimo were
there, too, yesterday.
You were there, right?
- Yes.
- See.
I didn't take it.
- I didn't take it, either.
- Manager, please believe us.
Everyone, here,
is responsible.
I'll have to think about
your wages this month.
What!?
Are you going to take it
out from our wages?
- What did you expect?
- Why?
Don't complain!
If you don't want that,
then look over yesterday's
receipts again to see if
there's any math errors.
Get to it!
We're short by 15,000 yen.
KONARI LAW OFFICE
Konari-san, here you are.
This should give us
the edge in court.
Use it wisely.
Thank you.
"Marimo, it's hard
to earn a living."
"We can't be wasteful."
"Will you give it some
serious thought?"
Is that what you told her?
I told her to think it over.
What did she say to that?
She made a face like this.
How cute.
Isn't that a laugh?
And I have this much money.
That's awesome.
I'm scared of myself.
You should go independent.
You have extreme luck.
This is advice from God.
This is your time of trail
and challenge,
now that you have a child.
It's your time to strive
your hardest.
Serious?
Here's your 60,000 yen.
I'm getting nervous here.
I'm going to open a savings
account for myself.
I feel like an adult.
Number 54!
I'm next.
I'm number 55.
Number 55!
Yes!
Please fill this out.
My name?
Do you want to know
my name?
Yes, please.
Do you believe in
God's advice?
I believed in it.
That is why I'm here.
Aren't I amazing?
This is a savings for
my girl and me.
Do I need to stamp my seal?
My seal?
- Yes.
- I see.
Give me the cash now!
All the customers are out.
The lunch hour sales
is 54,890 yen.
- Well?
- That's exactly what I have.
What's going on here?
Weren't you in front of the
Manager's desk yesterday?
There's been an armed
burglary at the bank!
Don't accuse me of it!
- Are you saying I did it?
- I'm saying it's not me!
But... Never mind.
- What were you going to say?
- Come out with it.
You've been wearing
new clothes lately.
I can afford this much!
It was cheap!
Is it wrong to buy
new clothes?
Marimo is the one
with nice clothes.
Now that you've mentioned it...
These are all the clothes
I've had from before.
I haven't bought anything
new since I came here!
- Are you saying that it's me?
- I didn't say that.
- Is it me then?
- I didn't say that either.
Stop accusing each other.
Let's think this over calmly.
Who is the oldest person
here who is in dire need
of living expenses and
child support money?
Don't look at me!
- Sotokoba-chan.
- It's not me!
- I'll quit.
- What?
I don't want to stay here
after being accused.
Not to say that the
hourly rate is low.
I'm not getting much
for my dancing, too.
- I'll find a job elsewhere.
- Wait a minute, Jun-chan.
It'll be hard to part
with you all, but...
What is this dance fee
that you're talking about?
It's the fee you get for
dancing at show time.
I haven't been receiving
anything for it.
Same here.
What's going on there?
I've been working at 820 yen
per hour for three years now!
820 yen?
Why do you sound
so surprised?
Do you have a higher
hourly rate than me?
A little.
Are you serious?
Marimo, how much do you get?
I get...
It doesn't matter, does it?
- You don't have to say.
- It it higher than me?
How much are you getting?
850 yen.
I'm sorry!
I was taking advantage
of you completely!
- I'm really sorry!
- Should it be like this?
Manager, do we really
need Marimo?
Before you think about
reducing our pay,
you should think about
things like that.
Let's calm down here.
If she leaves, you can
get a higher hourly rate.
We need Marimo!
She's our draw girl!
I thought we were
the draw girls.
- Are you picking a fight?
- You're not young anymore.
- You'd better cut it out.
- What's your problem?
- We need Marimo here!
- We don't need her!
This isn't looking good.
It really isn't.
I've become a problem here.
Part-time job?
Maybe I'll change jobs.
They pointed the gun at the
female employee and ran off
with roughly 1.3 million
yen in cash.
The police are after these
two men for robbery.
There were many customers
in the bank at the time.
I don't believe it.
What is he doing?
So he did that.
Let's hear what the
female employee has to say.
I thought he was
acting suspiciously.
Then he really did it.
I pressed the
emergency button.
I was really scared.
We've spotted one of
the robbers on the run!
Where did he go anyway?
Officer, my money is gone!
Find him, please!
Aren't you the bank robber?
No, it's not me.
One of the robbers attacked
an officer and fled!
Capture him!
Shinpei!
I guess he wouldn't
come home.
Shinpei!
- Where's Shinpei?
- He's not here.
Asami-chan, you'll do.
Come! I need your help!
- What's going on here?
- It's the Manager's fault.
Why must I be treated
like this?
Why are the four of them
getting something and not me?
I don't understand it at all.
- Well, that's because...
- You needn't pay them.
- They're lousy anyway.
- Is that right?
- How can you say that?
- I'm sorry.
I'm honest.
Damn guy! What a thing
to say to your senior!
I'm running away...
I guess I should be.
I punched that officer.
- I saw you on the news!
- Am I on the news?
What a face you had!
They've got it wrong.
The police misunderstood.
- Will you shelter me?
- Will you lend me money?
I have to pay for this
outfit by today.
But I used up all my
money on hand.
Don't you have
money on you?
- No, I don't.
- Didn't you rob a bank?
You've got it wrong.
Here's 10,000 yen.
Hold this for me.
See you later.
I'LL SELL YOU INFORMATION
Do you have information
on the bank robber?
Will you sell it to me?
Information on the bank
robber? Sure.
What a savior!
You're fast as ever.
Pay me first.
Can I get a cigarette?
Pay me.
My money.
I don't have any now.
He ran off with it.
- I'll pay you later.
- Give me back my cigarette.
I want my money.
All right, all right.
Wait here.
What is Shinpei thinking?
- He's a fool.
- He must be stressed out.
He must've wanted to
impress his daughter.
With a lot of money on hand.
He's a fool. I have no
room for sympathy for him.
Is it my fault?
Give me a break.
This is a picture
of the culprits.
Is he someone you know?
He's a very good boy.
But people can
change overnight.
So this is a town
with a criminal.
It's dangerous.
Is this where this
town is headed?
(I can't hear you!)
When this masked man
took out his gun...
How embarrassing. I'm
a criminal's daughter.
Then he put down
the gun and fled.
I'm going to leave
this place, after all.
Do we have any
money lying around?
- What are you doing?
- It's a misunderstanding.
Let me borrow that.
I'll return it later.
Give it back!
Mama left it for me!
I said I'll return it!
I don't trust you!
Give it back!
I haven't done anything!
I was thinking about our
future, so I went there.
I don't know how much
living expenses we need.
Or how much tuition or
allowance you need.
I have no concept
of how much I'll need.
So I thought if I had
some money set aside...
- Do you have money set aside?
- No.
What's your point?
So I went to the bank
for that purpose.
And rob the bank?
Stupid! I went there to
open a savings account.
Then the robber popped
up on the side of me.
He had a gun on him.
He fled with our money.
Our living expense money.
I ran after him.
But they thought
I was with him.
No one believes me.
Please believe me.
I really didn't do it.
I'll swear to God...
I'll swear to you!
I can honestly swear to it.
Kirishima Shinpei, you're
under arrest for robbery!
- It's all a misunderstanding!
- Arrest him!
Marimo, I really didn't
do it! Believe me!
Shinpei ran away?
It'll be to his disfavor
in court.
But he didn't rob the bank.
How do you know that?
You saw the news,
didn't you?
That was definitely him.
I've decided to believe
in him.
I want to believe his words.
If he gets caught,
please help him.
I can't withdraw money
without the seal!
So you're going
to believe in him.
What do you all think?
I'll represent him.
I'm glad for you.
With Sensei on the case,
he's in good hands.
The fee is 200,000 yen.
You need money
for everything.
Even if it means saving
someone who is right.
But I don't have the
money on me now.
That's my price.
Nothing less.
OK. I'll bring the money.
Sensei, why did you demand
such a huge amount from her?
She's just a child. And
she's Shinpei's daughter!
I wanted to test her.
IF YOU NEED MONEY,
PLEASE COME TO SEE US.
WE DO NOT RESORT TO ANY
ILLEGAL COLLECTION METHODS.
THE ANNUAL INTEREST
RATE IS 27.745%.
WE DO NOT LEND MONEY
TO ANYONE UNDER 18.
WE'LL BUY YOUR UNNECESSARY
ELECTRICAL APPLIANCES
Do you want money? I have
a good paying part-time job.
How do I raise 200,000 yen?
I'm doing an undercover
investigation.
It was my day off today.
When I got up around
noon, no one was home.
My wife and daughter
went out somewhere.
I wanted to spend time
with my daughter,
but she wasn't home.
There was only a cold plate
of curry over rice at home.
And I didn't want to eat
that on my day off.
Then I started getting
upset inside.
What were you trying
to do there, Marimo-chan?
Marimo-chan!
What should I do?
Should I ask for an advance?
WE'LL BUY YOUR UNNECESSARY
ELECTRICAL APPLIANCES
Money matters are
important, but...
Manager, you're too sly.
What's wrong with me?
You shouldn't have
suspected your employees!
What's wrong with worrying
about the missing 15,000 yen?
We're talking about money!
- Will you raise my hourly rate?
- Mine, too.
We'll allot the missing
15,000 yen among ourselves.
Please give him the
same hourly rate as us.
Please raise mine, too.
That's right. This is
a money matter, too.
That's right, Manager.
So they're starting to
come to an agreement.
- As for Marimo...
- What is it?
They have an issue
with Marimo-chan?
You should let her go and
let us be the draw girls.
Will you be quiet, old hag?
- That's a low blow.
- Old hag?
Aren't you worried, too?
Aren't you the most affected
by Marimo-chan's presence?
- That's right!
- What about me?
- She just jumped.
- No, I didn't!
- She's defensive.
- She's panicking.
We're not talking about me!
We're talking about
the hourly rate!
- Go back to the topic!
- Manager!
- Asami-chan jumped at it.
- Shut up, old hag!
I wonder how much
I can get for all these.
Excuse me.
Does Shinpei live here?
- Yes.
- I'm glad!
He's not home.
Did he get caught?
Not yet.
Will you return this to him?
Shinpei is wonderful.
He was on the run but
he lent me money.
That really helped.
- What's your name?
- And this.
Say...
Do you think Shinpei
committed the robbery?
No.
You're a great gal.
You're super cute!
Catch you later.
What is she thinking?
You're going off the
topic of conversation.
- You're disturbed again.
- I'm not.
Are you more conscious
of Shinpei-san now,
with Marimo-chan around?
- Your feelings are swayed.
- That's not true!
I think Shinpei is the
disturbed one.
He wants to have his
fun with Asami-chan,
but he wants to provide
for Marimo-chan.
The father in Shinpei
has awakened.
Shinpei-san, a father?
He's changed lately.
- In what way?
- Just here and there.
- You may be right.
- Right?
Do you think he stole
our 15,000 yen to cover
for his living expenses?
He wouldn't do that.
Don't ever say that again.
He wouldn't steal
from his friends.
- I'm sorry.
- Stupid!
- Marimo-chan!
- What's up?
Did you hear that?
I meant no harm by it.
Shut up.
Don't let it bother you.
How is Shinpei doing?
Well...
Will you lend me money?
Why?
He's about to be
caught by the police.
But it's all from
a misunderstanding.
- Police? Was he arrested?
- Again?
That's what I came here
for in the first place.
- What am I doing anyway?
- What happened to Shinpei?
There he is!
Will you come in quietly?
- Where's Konari-san?
- He's not here.
- I brought the money.
- Oh, that?
It's the attorney fee
to save Shinpei.
How can you demand 200,000
yen from a high school girl?
We all pitched in for it.
Count it!
Everyone went back to work.
What are you going to do?
You don't feel like going?
I don't blame you.
Let's grab something to eat.
The lights are on.
Is it a burglar?
Doesn't she have any
secret savings?
Shinpei?
What are you doing!?
Will you lend me money?
I can't draw money
from it without a seal.
It made me jump when
the bank asked for a seal.
What's the matter?
Marimo?
What's wrong?
I was worried about you.
I've been worried about
you all this time.
I felt very lonely.
As a parent... don't make
me worry about that.
Sorry.
Don't make me worry
about money matters.
You're right.
I...
...was very, very...
Is the doctor in?
Will you treat me?
I'm in pain.
Hey!
Are you stupid?
I remember this tattoo.
We've found you!
Get him!
I'm glad you were cleared.
I'm upset! After all that
they beat me up,
all I get is a simple apology.
Marimo-chan,
please look after Shinpei.
What?
Why don't you
struggle a bit for her?
Instead of just waiting
around for work from me,
why don't you open your
own private eye office?
What is he talking about?
Aren't you a private eye?
I'm an investigator.
Forget the details.
I'm worried.
Oh, no.
I saw that. Is that your
secret savings?
Manager, you shouldn't
hide your money there.
You've got is all wrong.
I'm sending this money home.
Nice!
A parent can learn
from his child, too.
I have an old story
to tell you tonight.
A father who used to carry
his child across the river
was about to lose his sense
of direction from the strong
river currents. Then the
child on his back said,
"Dad, the shallow side
is on that side."
And that enabled the both of
them to cross the river safely.
That was a lesson he learned
from the child on his back.
That's how the line,
"listen to your children" started.
A parent will mature with the
lessons he learns from his child.
We'll go into show time now!
Trust isn't something
that you think in your head.
I think I somehow
realized that today.
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
MATSUNAGA YÔICHI
A Production of
JOKER & TBS
2014-09