Please don't see Rintarô again.
I'm sure she's feeling screwy
to find out that I'm her father.
Please let her keep
her happiness.
Leave.
Marimo!
So it's just a cold.
She gave me a scare!
She must've worn herself
out from everything.
With Rintarô-kun and
Sotokoba-san.
It must've hit her
all at once.
A lot has been going
on for you, too.
What do you take your
parental responsibilities as?
That has nothing
to do with it!
How about beef with
potatoes and rolled eggs?
What is it?
You haven't cooked
for me in a long time.
Well, the situation isn't
the same as before.
I feel like a youth now.
Stop it. I'm cooking now.
I don't believe this.
I want to use the bathroom.
It's making me sick!
I'm sorry. I want
to use the bathroom.
Isn't that awful? I'm lying
in bed with a cold.
But those two were
getting it on together.
Can you believe that?
So I yelled and stopped
them in the act.
Is that right?
So you broke the
two up in the act?
- Isn't that improper?
- What did Dr. Asami do?
She left a while later.
Is that right? So you
chased her out.
Don't say it like that.
Is that right?
The little devil picked on
her future stepmother.
Don't say it like that.
Never mind already.
That's the face of a
daughter who is jealous
that her father is getting
close to the woman he loves.
Is that right?
You're not saying it right.
Try it again.
We're in the semi-finals now!
We have a full stadium with
an audience of 54,000!
And the throws!
He just gave a glare!
The coach gives an order!
And he throws!
- What do you think of that?
- What do you mean?
Did I get across the
feelings of the Yokohama
team and their coach?
There's a mamono
at the Kôshien.
- There's a marimo?
- Not marimo but mamono!
Don't you youngsters get it?
Love.
Do you understand?
That's right. Coach Watanabe's
love for his students is in
that single ball. The coach
said something good...
Is that right?
They're on the same
wavelength...
Those two were trying
to be lovey-dovey...
Does that mean...
that I interrupted?
Oh, no. That makes it
hard for me to stay here.
I got lucky!
I got an overnight
onsen trip for two.
I won it in the lottery
for the shopping district.
A onsen trip? How nice!
- Get ready.
- Serious?
It'll make a nice memory
for this summer.
- Let's have a grand time!
- Are we going from now?
On second thought, I'll pass.
You should go with Asami-san.
Yes, go with Asami-san!
You're blushing!
I want to take you.
No! Why do I have to go
with you to the onsen?
I don't want to share
a room with you!
What's the difference
from here?
There's a curtain to
separate our areas!
Stop talking back!
Just get ready!
- No one's home!
- It's me, Rintarô!
You left home?
I had a fight with my
dad and I left home.
I figured Shinpei-san would
understand how I feel.
I'm sorry for barging
my way in.
Rintarô-senpai came
to our house.
It appears that he might
end up living with us.
My summer is about
to take a sudden turn...
No. Go home. Your
parents must be worried.
It's an inconvenience. Go.
What is he thinking
of anyway?
This isn't a shelter
for runaways.
Why aren't you
helping him?
- Why should I?
- He's in a bind.
I know! You want
to live with him here.
- You have such a dirty mind!
- Never mind already.
What's with her?
What's with him?
He sure upsets me.
You're doing
the same thing!
- I'm sorry.
- Stop smiling!
- Do your job properly!
- Sotokoba-san!
HITONATSU NO PAPA E
MATSUSHIGE YUTAKA
KITAGAWA HIROMI
MATSUDA SATOSHI
ICHIHARA HAYATO
KOBAYASHI CHIHARU
YAMANAKA SÔ
KINBARA YASUNARI
TSUNOMURA MAKO
TOYOKAWA EIJUN
HIRANUMA NORIHISA
MATSUMOTO RIO
YAMAZAKI HAJIME
MASHIMA HIDEKAZU
SEKI KEISUKE
MORIYAMA MIHO
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
Directed by
MATSUNAGA YÔICHI
EPISODE 9:
UMI NI TOBIKONDE SHITTA
CHICHIOYA SHINJITSU
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
All the customers have left!
The customers really
liked it!
You were great!
Sotokoba-san didn't come.
Is he quitting, after all?
I doubt it. He came up on
stage and danced yesterday.
But he didn't show up today.
If he was going to stay,
he would've showed up.
Maybe he thought about
his daughter's wedding.
Changing jobs for
his daughter...
That's something I just
don't understand.
If he wants to quit,
that's fine.
But if that's the case,
we'll have to change
everyone's positions.
Please think about that.
- I'm going.
- Wait!
What's with him?
Isn't he awfully cold?
It's scary in here.
Sotokoba-san!
Thanks.
You scared me.
My heart is still beating fast.
Aren't you going
back to the pub?
YOTSUBISHI SHÔJI K.K.
Everyone is waiting for you.
I thought it was nice...
To see you troubled over
your daughter getting married.
But I don't like what I see now.
It's not like you...
so I don't like it.
So she turned you down.
Your plan didn't work.
These tickets cost me a lot.
Shall you and I go?
I guess that wouldn't work.
She doesn't understand
my feelings.
That's a father for you.
A father, huh...
Can I say something?
I know. You want to keep
this a secret from everyone.
This is hard for me to say...
I want you to erase from
your memory what happened
from yesterday till today.
- Are you listening?
- Sotokoba-san is here.
I'm sorry to call you out
before your wedding.
What did you want to tell me?
Here. This is where
I work now.
- This is a first-rate company.
- My friend got me in.
Wow! So you did as I asked.
Of course.
So you'll be working here
when I get married.
- That's right.
- Thank you!
BREAKFAST IS IN THE REFRIG-
ERATOR. DON'T DRINK TOO MUCH!
I'M OFF TO MY PART-TIME JOB.
- Did you go to college?
- No.
You're seriously in trouble.
Shut up. I can earn a living
without knowing that.
What do you take your
parental responsibilities as?
What's wrong? You look dead.
Regarding this...
...that says that
Marimo is my daughter...
Legally... having me
as a father is...
Did you wash your face?
What are you doing!?
Is it that harsh?
I don't understand it...
...even after thinking long
and hard about it!
Is Marimo really happy,
having me as a father?
I really don't know
what to do anymore.
You'll be fine.
You're trying your best,
without running away.
You're not the one who
has to make the decision.
That's awful. How can he
throw you into the sea?
Shall I run him in for you?
Marimo's boyfriend ran away
from home and came to me.
But I turned him away.
That's only normal. No one
would acknowledge that.
I was afraid his father
would say something again.
I thought I'd be accused of
being improper and irresponsible.
I don't mind him talking
badly about me, but...
I don't want him to judge
Marimo in the same light.
I can understand
Koba-san's feelings.
What are parents for?
We're living for our children.
That's stale!
- Stop trying to look good.
- What's wrong with that?
Shinpei-san isn't coming back.
Never mind about him.
He has every right
to be angry with me.
I was running to him for help.
Don't say that.
He's wrong to have
told you off like that.
I have to go now. I have
to attend my night classes.
I can't flunk my college
entrance exams twice.
I'll be back to formally
apologize to Shinpei-san.
College entrance
exams, huh...
What's going on?
Yes, I understand.
I'll be expecting you.
I, Manager Okamoto, have
accepted the message.
- How was it?
- That was Nakamori Ryûji!
The producer for the
Muscle Museum musical!
He's coming here tomorrow!
He's coming to check us out!
Does that mean someone
is going to be chosen?
This is your opportunity!
If someone from
our pub is chosen...
What's all the ruckus?
Nakamori Ryûji
is coming to this pub.
He's the producer for
the Muscle Museum!
I'm a fan of his!
Let's practice hard!
Let's shock him!
Everyone, get to
your positions!
Let's start!
What about Sotokoba-san?
If he's not coming, we have
to change the formation.
If he is coming, then
we can leave it as it is.
Manager.
Let's leave it open for him.
Wait a minute. Isn't that
being too soft-hearted?
- What do you mean?
- You said before...
That if we all took the
audition and someone failed...
Are we going to beg the
producer to include our friend?
Will all of you think
about it?
We have one less rival.
This is our opportunity.
But Sotokoba-san might come.
He won't come.
He's working elsewhere now.
- What do you mean?
- So he won't come back here.
He will come back.
I'll go and call him.
Hey! Don't do that.
I'm sure he wants to come
back. He's just holding out.
That's only natural.
He put an end to it.
He drew the line as a father.
That's what it means
to be a father.
Will you understand that?
What's wrong? You sound
like an ordinary parent.
Say...
You've changed.
I've just matured.
I hope I'm not the cause.
Don't put on an act.
I wouldn't want that!
Oh, shut up. Go back
to work already.
What's up?
Koba-san was attacked?
When I came to see him
after my night shift,
he was lying unconscious
on the floor.
He apparently had it out
with a group of thieves.
He had blood all over
his face.
Do you know what he said
as he was being transported
on to the ambulance?
He doesn't want his family
to know about this.
He doesn't want them
to know what he does.
When I heard that, it just
didn't seem right to me.
He's working there
for his daughter.
So how can she
not know about it?
I'm going over.
Excuse me.
Asami-chan! Marimo-chan!
So you both came to see me.
Was that the extent
of your injury?
You had blood all over
your face.
Oh, that?
When they cut my hand,
I must've panicked and
rubbed it all over my face.
You all look disgusted.
Can I ask you questions?
Come quickly.
- Aren't I the victim?
- That's right.
- I can't believe it.
- How can he show up here?
- I agree.
- The Manager must be upset.
- I would imagine.
- Those guys were terrible.
I hit the gasoline cans
as hard as I could...
but it had no effect.
So I panicked.
You were lucky you got away
with a light injury as that.
That's a life-staking job.
So you're working
hard as a father.
Can you tell?
Aren't you going
to dance anymore?
A child is a parent's
soft spot.
Take Shinpei as an example.
He went on his hands and
knees and asked Rintarô-kun's
father to acknowledge
his relationship to you.
When I saw that,
my heart was moved.
We're talking about
Shinpei here.
When I saw that, I felt
I couldn't lose to him.
Will you excuse yourself?
Why did you come here?
If you want to quit,
then that's fine.
But will you think about
their feelings, too?
Some were waiting for
you to come back.
I'm sorry. I asked him
to come here.
I'm sure you have your
reasons for quitting.
But when you did,
you rejected us.
Will you have some
consideration here?
I'm sorry. I'll leave
right away.
Are you really quitting?
Nakamori Ryûji
is coming tomorrow.
He's the producer for the
musical we applied for.
Let's dance together.
Good luck to all of you.
Hey!
I searched all over
for you!
You're not in bad shape!
- What're you doing here?
- He came to our house.
I heard you were
seriously injured.
So I couldn't let it go.
He told me what
your job entails.
Please don't mention
that at the wedding.
I'm going. I have to get
up early tomorrow.
Yôko, thanks for coming.
Wait a minute!
Your dad got injured.
Aren't you worried?
He's fine as you can see.
I was worried about him
so I went to the hospital.
But he wasn't there.
So I went to the police
station, and he wasn't there.
He was here.
Isn't this a pub?
He looks fine to me.
He did it for you.
What were you thinking when
you asked him to change jobs?
Sotokoba-san
told me before...
...that he wanted to work
at a job that he enjoyed.
It was his childhood
dream to dance on stage.
But he's working in a pitch
dark warehouse now.
- I feel sorry for him.
- Then he should just quit.
So you're making me
look like the bad guy.
Let's just drop it already!
Yôko-chan, don't get so upset.
You're a future bride.
You have to smile.
Just ignore what she said.
I think Koba-san is great.
Yes, he is! He's living
for you, Yôko-chan!
He's already made up his mind.
So stop arguing already.
She's just being willful.
Stop it.
You have no right to rob
your father of his dream!
I said to stop it!
No... Sotokoba-san is
just weak.
Don't insult him any
more or I'll get mad!
He was just all mouth!
That's not true! I wasn't just
mouthing off about my dream!
Yes, you were. Isn't that
why you ran away?
No!
You're gutless. So what if
your daughter is against it?
That's enough already.
Doesn't it ache your heart?
Tell me how it feels to
crush your father's dream
to make yourself look good.
- Don't say it like that.
- That's insulting!
You should take a good
look at yourself before
- you dwell on his title!
- What do you mean?
Would you have fallen for me
if I was a Tôdai graduate?
Don't insult me!
Stop trying to take
the easy way out!
What's with this place?
Am I the one at fault here?
He's the one who abandoned
his family to live as he pleased!
That's right. I'm to blame.
Don't let her control you.
It's unsightly.
He's trying to change.
He has things to do that are
more important than his dream.
Don't you understand that?
Do you have the right
to condemn him for it?
What do you mean by that?
Don't use your child
as an excuse.
Why did you go on your hands and
knees to Rintarô-senpai's parents?
Did you think that would
do me any good?
Is that what it
means to be a father?
I had my ideals
of a father, too.
When you suddenly appeared
in my life, I was shocked.
Because the father I was
idolizing, turned out to be you.
But you are you.
I was able to say what I want
because of who you represent.
You are more like a friend
to me than a father.
You're reckless but
you're warm-hearted.
And I liked you for your
warm-heartedness.
You do things that normal
people wouldn't do.
And that's why I was
drawn to you.
But if you're going to bow
down to his parents like that...
Then I could have had
someone else as a father.
I want to see you as you are.
You're right.
When I was a child, I used
to admire my papa.
It's always nice to keep
that image of one's father.
Please take a look at your
father's dream sometime.
It's pretty nice.
Thanks.
I grabbed them from
the refrigerator.
That's bad.
I think Shinpei is just
feeling confused now.
He looked through
the travel magazines
and bought those tickets
for the onsen trip.
He's cute in what he does.
He's just trying to act
a bit mature.
Doesn't it bother you?
If I monopolize him.
I don't know what to say.
Kanpai.
Marimo-chan's words
sure hit me.
The back of a father, huh...
Don't be weak-willed.
You're not wrong at all.
Let's have confidence here!
I'm upset! I could only say
half of what I wanted to say!
A father is living
for his family!
He's killing his emotions
Don't get depressed!
Shut up.
I'm worried about you.
You're bothering us, crybaby.
He's right. It's not as easy
as you make it sound.
I don't believe you said that.
I'm mad! I'm going home!
I'm not hearing you out again!
Is that what you want?
I'm going to stick it out
my style, after all.
Trying to adjust
my life to hers...
...was the beginning
of a life full of lies.
- No!
- I'm serious.
Why?
I'm going to stop
acting cool.
I don't understand it!
You don't have
to understand it!
That has nothing to do
with being a father!
As a father, I'm going
to struggle my hardest.
- But...
- I already made up my mind.
See you.
- I don't believe it!
- He's a big fool!
Don't be like him!
He's hopeless.
I'm sorry about the
other day.
What are you doing here
in the morning like that?
Can I say something?
What I said the other
day... was a lie.
I'll try my best to be
accepted as her father.
I'll even change my job.
I'll find a decent job.
I'm who I am. I can't be
someone I'm not.
You're truly upsetting!
Take good care of Marimo!
Sorry about the other time
when you left home.
You can come anytime.
You are always welcomed.
- Not in front of my father!
- Left home?
You're in big trouble. One
day, he'll walk out on you.
Bye!
Are you up? Good morning.
Why didn't you come
home last night?
The woman wouldn't let me go.
I'm very popular, you know.
Didn't I tell you to call me
if you're not coming home?
You're such a nagging kid.
I'm scared to be
home alone at nights.
I don't like being alone.
Don't leave me alone.
Eat.
I made rolled eggs and
beef with potatoes.
You can compare them
with Asami-san's.
- What are you saying?
- You're blushing again!
Don't you want to go
to college?
Don't hold back.
I wanted to go before,
but I'm not sure now.
Maybe it's because
I met all of them.
It's nice to have a dream.
I wonder what my dream is.
How would I know?
Figure that out yourself.
Don't be tight!
Don't brood over that.
- I'll push you.
- Wait.
Pick up the beat!
Smile!
- Stop!
- Don't stop them!
That's not it!
Sotokoba-san will be here!
- Kôji, you have to be here.
- Kôji, get it right.
- We don't have much time.
- Will he really come?
There's only 30 minutes
to go before opening.
He may be a failure
as a family man,
but he's great as an
individual man.
He'll be here for sure.
He popped up here, chasing
after his childhood dream.
He wouldn't easily...
Why are you holding
hands with Non?
I don't believe it.
- When did that happen?
- Non-chan is blushing!
Can I come in?
Welcome back.
- I'm back.
- Sotokoba-san!
You smell like seawater!
- You're soaking wet!
- I struggled a lot!
- Manager! News!
- What is it?
- I have a reservation.
- Who is it?
Natsu Mayumi-san!
With the Morning Musume?
Wow!
We're in it for big time!
I want to join the
Morning Musume!
RESERVED SEATS
- Are they here?
- Not yet.
Aren't we up next? Are
they really coming here?
What's going on?
Are they here?
Yôko, about my job...
This is my fiancé.
Thank you for always
being good to Yôko.
Congratulations on your
upcoming wedding with her.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Nonohara.
I'm... working here.
You were great yesterday.
You were desperately
trying to make your point.
I want to see your dream.
- But...
- I'd like to see it, too.
Thank you.
Welcome to the pub tonight.
I'm the manager, Okamoto.
We have raw gems here.
We have talented youths
and an old man.
I'm the manager, Okamoto.
We have...
Forget him. Let's celebrate.
We have a couple here
who will be getting married!
You have to grasp
your own happiness.
Yes.
I'm going to dance, too!
- Take me to the onsen.
- Sure.
I don't know where I stand.
I like his smiling face.
With him, I feel happiness.
I wonder if I should
start calling him Papa.
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
MATSUNAGA YÔICHI
A Production of
JOKER & TBS
2014-11