Non-san is in danger.
What are you doing?
We were going to practice
one last time so that we
won't have regrets when
one of us is fired.
Just look at me...
I'm in the newspapers.
I look cute!
That incident was reported
in the newspapers.
So we were getting
carried away by it.
The customers have been
looking at us all week!
She's cute.
- Enjoy!
- You're getting carried away.
Can you tell?
- Isn't it strange?
- It sure is.
Why doesn't the doctor
get any credit for it?
- Didn't I help, too?
- So did I.
They didn't do anything, but
they get all the attention.
This is truly upsetting.
Let's go.
Thank you for coming
to our pub today.
All kinds of things
happen during the summer.
When you want a case solved,
come to Kirishima Detective
Office on the third floor.
For your summer colds,
come and see the very
beautiful Dr. Asami.
Don't forget what I just said.
Let's get into it.
Start the music!
We had let it get to our head.
In hindsight...
It was like our final banquet.
HITONATSU NO PAPA E
MATSUSHIGE YUTAKA
KITAGAWA HIROMI
MATSUDA SATOSHI
KOBAYASHI CHIHARU
YAMANAKA SÔ
KINBARA YASUNARI
TSUNOMURA MAKO
TOYOKAWA EIJUN
HIRANUMA NORIHISA
TOYOHARA KÔSUKE
HAYASHI YASUFUMI
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
Directed by
ITSUKIDA RYÔICHI
EPISODE 7:
WAKARE! IKITE IREBA
ITSUKA AERU
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
It dries fast in the summer!
What are you doing?
I thought I'd work here
part-time.
Maybe I'll take up dancing.
It feels good to be on stage.
You were putting
everyone in a spot.
What are you saying?
For someone who hasn't
done anything,
you have too much attention.
I'm the one who solved
the case.
No! I did! I remembered the
culprit's license plate number!
I'm the one who stormed in!
Shut up! You're distracting me.
I can't concentrate.
Do you understand?
My exams are coming up.
I'm under pressure now.
It'll determine if I can
become an attorney or not.
Will you be a bit more
considerate here?
Why should we get scolded?
Just study at your own home!
- The air conditioner is broken.
- Then go to your office!
Sensei told me not to come
until the exams are over.
Do you know why he said that?
Because he has high
expectations of me.
Sensei, you seem restless.
Shall I call Satoi-san in?
Don't act on your own.
I wonder if he's studying.
Don't you have another
one like this?
Why don't you give it to him?
Satoi-san will be elated.
He should only be elated
when he passes.
You're so stubborn.
- You don't have to go.
- I feel uneasy here.
With him around, it doesn't
feel like it's my home.
He'll hear you, fool!
Sorry.
- See you later!
- Take off my T-shirt!
Excuse me...
- Please hang in there.
- I am.
Don't say that to someone
who is already doing that.
I meant no harm by it.
What's with him?
He upsets me.
Hey!
Why bring that up now?
What're you saying!
Who do you think I am?
I don't understand it, too.
Just because you were
in the newspapers...
- Don't let it get to your head!
- We weren't doing that.
Why aren't you practicing?
It's your time to practice
from noon to opening time.
- But that's...
- What is it?
The pub has been
very busy lately.
And we're exhausted.
Jun, you should quit.
- That's awful.
- Stay out of this.
Don't decide that on your own!
Who do you think I am?
Are you looking for Shinpei?
You're very attractive.
- I think he's at the pub.
- Thanks. I'll go there.
Maybe I'll go, too.
I think I'll take a break.
I've been studying hard
all morning.
I think I'll feel refreshed
after I have tea with you.
It's not a bad feeling to get
popular from an incident as that.
As a matter of fact,
it feels great.
But that's where it all ends.
What happened to that spirit?
Should you be taking it easy?
Did you give up your
dream of going up?
- What are you doing here?
- To refresh myself.
- With Asami?
- I'm ready to go.
Am I wrong in what I say?
- What do you think?
- You're asking me?
I know what you're saying.
You can't grasp your dream
by taking the easy way out.
I don't want to hear it
from you.
What is that supposed
to mean?
You've failed the exam
many times. Don't act big.
- That isn't the issue here.
- Oh yes, it is.
Now, now.
Don't be so insulting
in your tone.
Everyone just got
a bit carried away.
It won't happen again, right?
You were on the
band wagon, too.
You've started running,
so you can't stop.
- Isn't that right, Asami?
- Don't ask me.
Anybody would get tired,
running everyday.
See? You shouldn't
have said that.
I'm siding with the Manager.
You've all changed.
- You're all acting strange.
- Don't tell us that.
You're just siding with
the man that you love.
- What do you mean?
- The Manager and Non-chan.
- Is that right?
- They were lovers before.
The Manager jilted her,
but she still loves him.
What a pleasant story!
That has nothing to do
with it!
You're all being naive!
So you want us to agree
to Jun being fired?
Fired?
Isn't that what we are
talking about?
Yes, that's what it's about.
Manager, that's taking it
to the extremes.
Everyone feels bad now.
You shouldn't do that.
They won't change.
They learned to make
excuses for themselves.
The pub is busy? So it's
OK to take a break?
If it gets that far,
it'll be over for them.
They're only human. They
need to take a break sometimes.
The Manager isn't wrong.
That's what it means
to be a challenger!
Don't get so hot about it.
Oh, give me a break!
I'll quit from my side!
- I'm leaving.
- Don't do that.
I'm sorry. I'll work
hard at it. So, please...
No.
Why? He's apologizing.
He's reflecting.
Why are you so cold to him?
A child should stay out
of this!
- Is an adult always right?
- Manager, please!
Say there's an audition
for a huge production.
Everyone passed except Jun.
Will you beg the judges
to let Jun pass, too?
If you think that's friendship,
then you're making a big mistake!
That's just sympathy!
There are others who would
want to dance here!
They're radiant and ambitious!
I want to work with
people like that!
- This is a workplace!
- But...
I'm sorry.
That's harsh.
We were striving hard
together until earlier.
This is like the business world.
Manager, if that is the case...
Don't say it! Don't say
any more than that!
I can't hang in there.
Didn't you quit your job
to enter this field?
Then you have to be cut
and dry about it.
But...
- That's not right.
- No, it's not.
- It's harsh in the workplace.
- We're all friends.
You mean co-workers. Rivals!
It's just a pub.
It's not an audition for
a huge stage production.
I can understand the
Manager's feelings.
Even when I'm the youngest.
So does everyone.
So why can't you forgive him?
You're all acting strange.
- Let's brood about it more.
- Marimo, stay out of this.
He's trying to break them up
abruptly. That's not right.
- You're being naive!
- I don't care!
I think I'm in the right.
Everyone worked hard together.
If you break them up,
they'll be all alone.
They can strive hard if
they are with each other!
It's lonely being on your own.
Marimo, thanks.
I'll re-train myself.
Thank you for everything
until now.
- Wait!
- Don't come after me!
Or we all won't be able
to change!
Why?
I don't understand it!
I can understand it.
That's what it means
to take the challenge.
I don't understand it at all!
You're such a worrywart, Ma.
Don't worry, I'm very
confident this time.
I really am.
OK.
The next time I go home,
I'll have an attorney's badge.
I'll talk to you again.
What are you thinking about?
It's great to be able
to cry for your friend.
Marimo-chan understands pain.
The pain of separation.
She's a kind child.
You haven't been
seducing me lately.
You were very aggressive
before.
That's true.
Hey, it's still business hours.
I'm sorry, but...
Are you in the middle of
an examination?
- Something like that.
- I think I'm fine now.
Please take care.
Asami-chan's former fiancé.
I got to see what he's like.
Have you thought about
my marriage proposal?
Asami, let's start all over.
I'm in love with someone.
Remember the time
we drank all night long?
There's a rumor that I spent
a night with my ex-finacé.
But he doesn't get jealous.
Who?
The man who just left.
No way! He looks shady.
He's been focusing his
love on his child lately.
- Is he married?
- No, he's not.
I don't understand what
you're saying.
There are a lot of loose
ends, don't you think?
I heard what happened.
- Where did they go?
- They left.
They have to lighten up here!
I wonder what it means
to have inner courage.
Is it going to be over
with them?
I don't think there's such
a thing as luck in life.
We have to try our utmost
best like fools to win.
That's the kind of pub
I wanted it to be.
But they're like rotten
apples now.
You mean, oranges.
They're just weak beings helping
and consoling each other.
They don't realize they're
heading for an easy life.
They've forgotten the inner
courage in them,
and are satisfied dancing
in this small place.
They're definitely going
nowhere doing that.
That's still not a good
reason to make them quit.
Marimo... you're kind.
You are right in what
you say.
But society doesn't
quite work that way.
When you cried for them...
It made me indescribably happy.
I know in my head that
it can't be helped,
and that's how it is
in the adult world.
I can see Satoi-san's point.
- That's true.
- Do you understand?
No one likes farewells.
You're acting like a parent.
I've been thinking
from yesterday...
and I concluded that we
were wrong for slacking.
But it's not right to fire
Jun to set an example.
But I don't know
what we should do.
Marimo, I read the newspapers.
And I got your address
from them.
So you moved out of that room.
I searched all over for you.
Who is he?
I don't know. But there seems
to be something going on.
Is this where you live?
Yes.
He's like a friend to me.
That's my father.
I'm Ishizawa.
He was Mama's lover.
I fell asleep.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to drop by
unexpectedly.
Are you married?
Yes.
Were you seeing Yukino
when you have a wife?
Don't judge me like that.
Not after you abandoned her.
What was that?
Have you any idea,
how she felt in life,
or less yet, how she felt
to deliver the child alone?
Have you any idea what
she wanted for Marimo?
Or the dreams she had
for Marimo?
And why she needed me?
I don't want to be
judged by you.
I'm sorry for bringing
him here.
Wait at home.
I don't want to be
judged by you.
Don't take it out
on Marimo-chan now!
Tell me where I can
reach him.
You know his number,
don't you? Tell me.
- Why do you want to know?
- I don't know!
But I want to tell him
something.
Don't.
- He was Mama's lover.
- He's married!
He took Yukino for granted!
He took her lightly!
He looked at her cheaply
for having a child.
He's a married man that
played with her feelings!
I didn't like it either!
But Mama was happy with him.
So that's that.
Mama used to get lonely, too.
That's when she met him.
And it just so happened
that he was married.
That's all there is to it.
Don't criticize Mama's life.
I want to believe that
Mama was happy...
Yukino-san's ex-lover?
Shinpei is a basket case
because of it.
Those two are real father
and daughter, right?
Of course they are!
Just concentrate on tomorrow.
Everyone is striving hard
for themselves in life.
But...
Make your mother back
at home happy.
Yes.
Is that right? Is that
what happened?
Marimo-chan is so admirable.
Shinpei-san is such a fool.
Why did he say that?
That's true.
Women are truly weak beings.
On the nights that we drink
in pain and sadness...
We feel so lonely that
we can't sleep alone.
I can understand how she felt.
I searched all over for you.
I'm Ustunomiya.
I'm Asami's former...
Sorry, I have no spirit
left in me today.
Please leave.
- What are you doing here?
- How do you feel about Asami?
Will you give me a break today?
What're you planning to do
with her when you have a child?
What are you saying?
I see.
I have a child, don't I?
Aren't you going to fight back?
Say something back to me!
I don't have the time to be
thinking about her now.
Sorry. I have my hands
all tied up now.
You've got some gall!
That's how I feel.
Where did that Shinpei go?
What do you have to do
for the second exam?
Essay.
From when did you want
to become an attorney?
From the time I decided
to go to college.
That's awesome. You had
a dream from that young age.
It's a long dream since
I haven't passed yet.
I admire you for chasing
after an impossible dream.
Impossible?
I'm sorry. I'm bothering
you, aren't I? Excuse me.
You look fine.
Fool.
Yukino-chan is dead.
The dead are eternally happy.
Save your words for the living.
Words?
That's right.
I'm referring to Marimo-chan.
Satoi-san, you're late!
- What time is it now?
- 8:45. I'm sorry, I overslept.
I have a favor to ask of you.
- Please tell me to hang in there.
- But I thought...
Don't tell a person who's
trying hard to hang in there.
You're hanging in there,
no matter what happens.
So I want to get that
power from you.
- Are you sure?
- Please do.
Satoi, this is your last spurt!
Let's have a pre-celebration
tonight!
Excuse me!
What's going on?
You said it has to do
with Marimo.
What time is it now?
He's here! Shinpei!
Don't you have something
to tell him?
Spill out everything that
you're keeping down inside!
- See you later.
- Please tell me...
Tell you what?
What is the dream that
Yukino had for Marimo?
Why do you want to know?
I want to realize it for her...
...as Marimo's father.
I want to realize it for Yukino.
Please tell me.
Can you really realize it?
Please tell me!
Please! I'll try my best!
Please!
Hang in there!
Which direction is the
examination hall?
Hang in there!
- I'm late!
- Please hurry!
When he said he had
his hands full,
does it mean I was jilted?
Is that right? Is that
what he said to you?
It's confusing, isn't it?
Would you like to get
a hearing test?
It can't be helped for now.
He took in a great
responsibility.
You have to bear it for now.
Haste makes waste.
That's true.
Where were you yesterday?
That's too long ago
to remember.
Call me if you're not
coming home.
I know how to kill time.
- But I can't hasten time.
- Are you stupid?
- Hello.
- You're acting mature.
Do you still have
your hands full?
- What're you talking about?
- Don't say irresponsible things.
What is it?
- It's still before opening time!
- Don't be so strict.
We're having a pre-celebration
party for my Satoi.
Oh, brother.
- What are you doing?
- We're boycotting.
What are you saying?
It's before opening time.
- We have just one demand.
- No!
We're against the unfair
dismissal and...
Stop it! Stop being naive!
You can be easily replaced.
Isn't that right, Manager?
I'm going home.
You are?
I'll find something I want
to do back at home.
- Satoi, what happened?
- I told that to Sensei, too.
The results of the exams
won't be out for a while.
Are you giving up your dream
of becoming an attorney?
Today's exam was very hard.
But everyone around me
was just going at it.
I realized today...
that they must've tried a
hundred times harder than me.
A hundred times!
My dream is too big.
- I've come to terms with it.
- Don't say that.
But they're not like me.
They have glittering eyes.
They can do it.
They can hang in there
because of their friends.
So please give them
another chance.
What is your favorite song?
It's for your farewell party.
I want something beaty.
This is your last chance!
I'm glad!
Thank you!
You're old already so you
really have to try hard.
My Satoi!
Stop it. Everyone's looking.
So what if they're looking.
There's nothing going on
between us.
It's going to be lonely.
- We'll see him again, won't we?
- Yes, we will.
We'll still be living in life.
People mature with pain.
Let's suffer more!
Satoi is running away
from his pains,
but let us struggle more!
- Oh, shut up!
- Let's hit it!
SENSEI, THANK YOU FOR
EVERYTHING. SATOI.
Hang in there!
I will.
Your mouth is open!
- Oh, it's you.
- Can you see something?
Is there happiness
beyond the clouds?
It must be nice to have
time on your hands.
Is Yukino there?
I'll give you an ordinary
but peaceful life.
That's the dream Yukino
had for you.
It feels good.
What's so good about
an ordinary life?
That might be impossible
with you.
There was a refreshing
breeze blowing through.
I had no idea that we only had
a short time left together.
Producer
ÔKAWA HIROSHI
Written by
KASHIDA SHÔGO
Music by
KAWAGUCHI DAISUKE
Theme Song
"Kanshô"
Performed by UETO AYA
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Softsubs Edited and Timed
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
RAW Provider
AVALLAC'H
Original TV Capture
AP
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
ITSUKIDA RYÔICHI
A Production of
JOKER & TBS
2014-10